字幕制作：leslie727
&
葫 芦
消失者 必重现
disappears, reappears.
四骑士 四骑士
Horsemen! Horsemen!
四骑士 四骑士 四骑士 四骑士
Horsemen! Horsemen!Horsemen! Horsemen!
以为我们弃场了？
Did you think we abandoned you?
还是魔术技穷了？
Or that we'd run out of magic?
好好想想 女士先生们
Well, think again, ladies and gentlemen,
准备好大开眼界吧
because you are about to be amazed.
既然各位在场 说明你们已经
If you're here right now, then you have.
循踪破译 解开了谜题
followed the clues and cracked the code.
恭喜 欢迎入局
Congratulations, and welcome.
纽约市 - 布什维克
阔别十年后 四骑士现在
It's been 10 years since the horseman last appeared,
正式回归
but we are back!
好了 凑近点 再近点
Okay, so, come in close.Mm, closer.
因为你自以为看清的越多
Because the more you think you see,
就越容易被旧瓶装新酒的把戏
the easier it will be to dress up old tricks.
蒙骗过去
and fool you that they are new.
我是 J·丹尼尔·阿特拉斯
So, my name is J. Daniel Atlas,
容我代表这几位魅力稍逊的同僚
and allow me to speak as I often do.
说一句…
for my less charismatic colleagues when I say…
呼 回归的感觉真好
Whoo! It is very good to be back!
没错 我们要么隐匿一阵
Yes. Yes.We vanished for a while,
但在魔法界
but in the world of magic,
凡消失者 必重现
everything that disappears, reappears.
只要戏法玩得对
Well, at least if the trick is done right.
我是梅里特·麦金尼
I'm Merritt McKinney.
不像我的好哥们丹尼那么自恋
Unlike my, uh, very good buddy here, Danny,
今晚入场的各位都挺谦虚
most of you checked your egos at the door tonight.
你们摸进这场地下盛会
You found this little underground soiree.
就是想来“受骗”的
because you wanted to get fooled.
大家好 我是杰克·怀尔德
Hey, everyone. I'm Jack Wilder.
战争 瘟疫 气候剧变 AI
Wars, pandemics, climate change, AI.
承认吧 此刻我们更需要魔法
Let's face it, we all need magic more than ever.
所以请睁大眼睛
So I want you to pay very close attention.
接下来的戏法不容错过
You are not gonna want to miss this next trick.
亨利·里维斯 现在冠了夫姓
Henley Reeves, now Henley Reeves Stanley.
三娃两狗 硕士在手
Three kids, two dogs and a master's degree.
久违了
It's been a while.
想我们吗？
Did you miss us?
他们当年确实挺牛
Those guys were great back in the day.
我以前也想当魔术师
I used to want to be a magician.
直到我过了中二年纪
And then I turned 12.
小心点 隔墙有耳
Careful, they might be listening.
哎哟 我吓得直发抖呢
Ooh, I'm shaking in my AllSaints.
他们能拿我怎样？
What are they gonna do?
是真金的？
Is that real gold?
- 啥？ - 手机是真金的吗？
- What? - Is that real gold?
那当然 爷有钱
Yeah, I'm rich.
这可是魔术秀 哥们
This is a magic show, dude.
这的人不是扒手
Every fool here is a pickpocket,
就是肥羊
or a pickpocket's fool.
- 刚那是俳句吗？ - 什么鬼？
- Was that a haiku? - What was that?
各位手里都有一张牌
Each of you just received a playing card.
不介意的话 请亮出来？
If you wouldn't mind, uh, pulling it out?
好 现在来大洗牌
Right. Now, we're gonna shuffle the deck,
随便找个身边人
so everybody find a random person near them.
跟他交换卡牌
and switch cards with them.
换完之后
And then when you've done that,
再找别人换一次
find somebody else and switch with them.
好的 现在…
Okay, great. Uh, now…
那个谁 就是你
Uh, duh-duh-duh-duh-duh…You there, down there.
- 我？ - 对 你的牌是？
- Me? - Yeah. What is your card?
- 方片A - 方片A 行
- Ace of diamonds. - Ace of diamonds. Okay.
那让事情复杂点
Let's make things a little more complicated here.
这里还有谁拿的是方片 A？
Does anybody else here have the ace of diamonds?
等等 是我 方片 A
Wait, it's me. Ace of diamonds!
哟
Ooh!
看来除了露拉 还有第五位骑士
Looks like we have a Fifth Horseman not named Lula.
上台来吧 你是助手了
Come up on stage, you're gonna be our helper.
- 搞起 - 上啊
Do it! Yeah, go!
现在 看着我的眼睛
Now, uh, look into my eyes.
然后… 睡吧
and… sleep.
宝刀未老
Still got it.
这孩子看着普通
Now, this might look like an ordinary kid to you,
但今晚 他将如鬼神附体般
but tonight, he is going to do extraordinary magic.
施展魔法
like a man possessed.
字面意思的“附体”
Literally.
- 亨利 - 在
- Henley. - Yes, Merritt.
麻烦你进到他身体里去
Would you mind stepping inside his body?
成了 杰克
Yep. And, Jack, uh,
你也把自己扔进去吧
why don't you throw yourself on in there, too?
这我拿手
What I do best.
上帝保佑你
And… Oh, God help you.
阿特拉斯 你也进去吧
Atlas, why don't you slither on inside, as well?
我只好也挤进去了
And I might as well wedge myself in there, too.
人多力量大 方能创奇迹
It takes a village to make magic.
J·丹尼尔·阿特拉斯在此
J. Daniel Atlas in the house.
想看魔术吗？
So, who wants to see a magic trick?
交给你了 梅里特
Take it away, Merritt.
哈啰 帅哥美女们
Hello, you beautiful people.
众所周知梅里特·麦金尼会读心术
Now, everyone knows that Merritt McKinney reads minds.
现在 我是他 还是他是谁？天晓得
Well, now, I'm him.Or he's me. Who knows?
呃 我感觉到今晚有人
Uh, I'm sensing someone came here tonight.
不是来享受魔法的 而是来拆台的
not to enjoy magic, but to tear it down.
布雷特·菲尼根在场吗？
Is there a Brett Finnegan in the house?
干嘛？
What up?
你和你的狐朋狗友
Now, you and your friends here.
搞了个“霍巴特营加密交易所”
set up the Camp Hobart Crypto Exchange.
- 没错 咋地？ - 就这业务
- Fact. Yep. Yeah. - It's what we're about.
卷走了纽约市民
Took the good people of New York's.
一半的养老福利金
employee pension and welfare fund half its cash.
呃 那是四舍五入夸大了
Uh, you're rounding up,
而且风险提示写得很清楚
and also, the risks were laid out very clearly.
愿者上钩嘛 老兄
Everybody knew what they were getting into, dude.
那你有没有把利润藏到海外？
Did you hide the profits offshore?
尾号为
Account ending.
53297 的帐户？
in 53297?
你不可能知道 除非你有我的…
You couldn't know that without my, uh…
哦 这是真金的吗？
Oh, is this real gold?
布雷特 看好你的东西啊
Brett, you ought to be more careful.
老兄
with your things, man.
梅里特会读心 但我杰克嘛
Merritt's a psychic, but me, Jack,
手快
I'm into sleight of hand.
问问你朋友
Ask your friends.
他们刚为缩小贫富差距做了贡献
They've just done their part to close the wealth gap.
什么？搞什么…
What? What the…
来 这就叫“再分配”
Now, here's a little redistribution.
喂 喂
Hey! Hey, hey!
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
等着收律师函吧 我要揍死你
Lawyer up, dude!I'll kick your ass!
噢噢
Uh-oh!
有人忘了亨利会飞哦
Someone forgot Henley can fly.
接下来交给我们 但请给台上这位
We can take it from here, but a round of applause.
最棒的骑士一点掌声
for the best Horseman on stage.
呼 哇哦
Whoo! Wow.
喂喂喂 行行行
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, hey.
真精彩 各位 举起酒杯
Fantastic. So, everybody, I want you to take your drink,
把酒倒在你们的牌面上
and I want you to pour it onto the face of your card.
倒吧
Can you do that?
每张牌显现出的12 个独特单词
Those 12 unique words on each of your cards.
就是新加密钱包的密码
form the password to your new crypto wallet.
噢 登上去
Oh! Log on.
你们会发现布雷特偷的几百万
and you'll find Brett's stolen millions more…
已公平退还
fairly redistributed.
天啊 五… 五万块
Oh, my God. Fifty…50, 000 bucks!
五万
50, 000!
你死定了 混蛋
You're freaking done, dude!
喔喔 消消气 小姜饼
Whoa, whoa!Cool your head, gingerbread,
我预见到了一个画面
'cause I am having a vision.
条子马上要破门而入了
Eh, maybe cops are gonna come bursting through that door!
所以你也变个魔术吧
So perform a magic trickof your own.
赶紧消失 三 二 一
and disappear in three, two, one.
好了 凑近点 再近点
Now come in close. Mm, closer.
因为你自以为看清的越多就越容易被…
Because the more you think you see, the easier it will be.
- 旧瓶装新酒的把戏… - 什么？
- to dress up old tricks… - What?
蒙骗过去
and fool you that they are new.
天啊 不
Oh, my God, no.
我觉得吧 你干得不错
Look, in my opinion, I think you did a great job.
我扮的阿特拉斯挺好
Uh, I think my Atlas was good.
但梅里特还得练练
My Merritt could probably use some work.
嗯-听着像个圣地牙哥的大烟鬼
Mm. - It's like a San Diego stoner.
和捕虾船长的串儿
and a shrimp boat captain had a baby.
是是
Sure.
说真的 博斯科 你怎么做到的？
No, seriously, Bosco, I don't know how you do it.
模仿秀不仅要声音像
A good impersonation isn't just about the mimicry.
还得抓细节
It's about attention to detail,
个性 神韵
personality and nuance.
行行行 我试试
Okay. Okay.Let me try, let me try.
呃… 我是 J·丹尼尔·阿特拉斯
Um…I'm J. Daniel Atlas.
离得越近 看得越瞎
The closer you look, the less you see.
有内味了
It was something.
嗯 再练练吧
Yep. Uh, you'll work on it.
- 我刚那下不赖 - 是个好开头
- I wasn't bad. - It was a good start.
- 但还得打磨 - 行吧
- But it could use some work. - Okay, sure.
- 你老盯着啥呢？ - 没事 没啥
- What do you keep looking at? - Nothing, nothing, nothing.
哥们 振作点 看看我们 多风光
Dude, cheer up.Guys, come on! Look at us!
看看我们走了多远 今晚简直赚翻了
Look at how far we've come.We totally scored tonight.
好吧 下次 你戴那顶粉色假发 行吗？
All right, next time, you wear the pink wig, okay?
不行
No.
- 伙计 又锁上了 - 行 我来撬
- Dude, it's locked again. - Okay, I'll pick it.
等等 别急 来那一招
Wait, wait, wait, hold on.Do the thing.
- 不要 - 求你了 来那一招
- No. - Please do the thing.
- 没必要吧 - 超帅的
- It's so unnecessary. - It's so cool.
- 我帮你拿包 - 真没必要
- I'll hold your bag. - It's so unnecessary.
- 来嘛 多好玩 - 好吧
- Come on, it's fun. - Okay.
你行的
You got this.
- 她就像个小马里奥 - 确实像马里奥
- She's like a little Mario. - She is like Mario.
小心 小心 求你别死
Careful, careful.Please don't die.
没事吧？ 没事
Are you okay? Yeah.
我要是有这身手 我就天天翻墙
If I could do that, I would only do that.
太酷了-简直疯了
It's so cool. - It's insane.
开心了？
Happy?
- 嗯 太棒了 - 是啊
- Yeah, that was awesome. - Yeah.
快放我们进去 好冷
Please let us in. It's cold.
呼
Whoo.
全城最好的公寓
Best apartment in the whole city.
没错 除了我们也没人能看到了
Yep, and no one will ever see it but us.
♪ 每个人… ♪
♪ Everybody… ♪
真可惜
It's such a shame.
♪ 但身披铠甲我是硬汉… ♪
♪ But in my armor I am a man… ♪
凑近点
Come in close.
再近点
Closer.
那家伙完蛋了
That guy is so screwed.
现在谁发财了？
Who's rich now?
查理 能把那玩意关了吗？求你了
Charlie, can you turn that thing off, please?
今晚我已经听够阿特拉斯了
I think I've had enough Atlas for one night.
收到
Yeah, I got you.
消失者 必重现
disappears, reappears.
只要戏法玩得对
At least if the trick is done right.
博斯科 看看有披萨吗？我饿死了
Bosco, can you check for pizza? I'm so hungry.
唉 我也是
Ugh, me, too.
我们是四骑士
We are the Four Horsemen!
没披萨但有啤酒
No pizza, but we got beer.
- 而且 真的只有啤酒 - 再近点 因为
- And, no, literally just beer. - Closer. Because.
- 你自以为看清的越多… - 谁要？
- the more you think you see… - Any takers?
我要一瓶
Yeah, I'll have one.
伙计 说真的 把那玩意关了
Dude, seriously, turn that thing off.
我关了啊
I did.
行吧 真逗 各位这边的投影仪在哪儿？
Okay. Real funny, guys.Where's the other projector?
我不是全息影像
I'm not a hologram.
“我不是全息影像”对 是是是
"I'm not a hologram."Right. Yes.
全息影像 都会这么说
Exactly what a hologram would say.
- 天啊 你是真人 - 别再摸我的脸
- Oh, my God, you're real. - Never touch my face again.
抱歉抱歉 我以为你是全息影像
I'm so sorry. I thought that you were a hologram.
我不该那样的 我是你的超级粉丝
I would never do that.I'm a huge fan of yours.
你好吗？
How are you?
你怎么找到我们的？
How did you find us?
不知道 我就花了大概 30 秒
I don't know.Took me about 30 seconds.
既然我这么容易就找到了你们
And if it was this easy for me to find you,
警察找过来又有多难呢？
how hard would it be for the police?
- 哇 等等 警察？ - 对 警察
- Whoa, hold on, the police? - Yeah, the police.
警察为什么要找我们？
Why would the police be looking for us?
呃 不知道 也许是因为
Uh, I don't know, what about that.
你们刚搞的那场抢劫？
little heist you just pulled?
或者因为你们私闯民宅
Or the fact that you're squatting in this place.
又或者你们偷的电
or that your electricity
comes from.
是从墙角电箱接出来的？
the circuit box in the corner?
谁知道呢 啥都有可能 我说的对吗 波波？
I don't know, it could be anything. Am I right, Bozo?
博斯科
Bosco.
- 嗯哼-博斯科·勒罗伊
Hmm. - Bosco Leroy.
啊 没错 对 博斯科·勒罗伊
Ah, that's right, yeah, Bosco Leroy.
怎么 你是从 ChatGPT 上
What, did you type, uh,
搜了个“虚构魔术师名字”吗？
"fictional magician name"into ChatGPT?
不 那是我的真名 阿特拉斯
No, that's actually my real name, Atlas.
嗯哼
Hmm.
怎么 跟你妈有一腿的是地图吗？
What, did your mom have sex with a map?
这一点也不好笑
- That's not funny.
你根本不了解我们 老兄
You don't know anything about us, dude.
- 我了如指掌 - 噢
- I know everything about you. - Oh.
名字可疑的博斯科·勒罗伊
The dubiously named Bosco Leroy,
大好的演艺前程
a promising acting career.
被沉重的助学贷款给毁了
cut short by crippling student loans.
从朱利亚德退学是挺遗憾
It's a bummer you had to drop out of Juilliard,
但你从未停止表演
but you never stopped performing.
呃 没记错的话 你上一份有薪工作
Uh, if memory serves, your last paid gig,
是在时代广场扮艾摩吧？
I think, was dressing as Elmo in Times Square?
首先 我没扮过艾摩
Okay, first of all, I was never Elmo.
那是红色天线宝宝
It's the red Teletubby.
小波
Po!
- 啥？ - 红色天线宝宝
- What? - The red Teletubby.
- 她叫小波 - 哦 小波
- Her name is Po. - Oh, Po!
她是我的最爱
She's my favorite one.
是吧？
Right?
- 她叫小波 - 可爱
- Her name is Po. - Cute.
还有你 琼·鲁克莱尔
And you, June Rouclere.
被爸妈强塞进的
Kicked out of every boarding school.
每所寄宿学校都开除了
your parents forced you to attend.
我看你不太喜欢服从权威啊
Not a big fan of authority, I take it.
呃 让我猜猜
Uh, let me guess.
你觉得“老古董”们搞坏了这地球
Uh, you think the "olds"broke the planet.
你们这一代有责任来收拾烂摊子
and it's your generation's duty to clean up their mess.
- 说对了吗？ - 说错了吗？
- Am I right? - Am I wrong?
全中
No.
所以你离家出走
And so, you ran away from home,
一路到了纽约 在坦宁魔术店
made your way to New York, where you ran into this guy.
遇见了这家伙 查理·盖伊斯
at Tannin's Magic Shop, Charlie Gayes.
- 对 嗨 - 嗨
- Yeah, hi. - Yeah, hi.
网上关于你的资料不多
I actually couldn't find a lot about you online.
但我知道你是孤儿
Although, I do know you were an orphan and.
童年一直在寄养家庭间辗转流离
you were in and out of foster care your entire childhood,
直到遇上这俩货
and that you didn't know the meaning of family.
你才懂了什么是家
until you hooked up with these two.
于是你们三个这几年来
And so, the three of you have been working.
一直在演你们的罗宾汉小把戏
your little Robin Hood act for years now,
试图用一个个戏法改变世界
trying to change the world one trick at a time,
直到这回玩了把大的 也就是盗用我的身份
all leading to your riskiest theft to date, my identity.
当时你在场？
You were there?
你们把我们的脸
You had our faces plastered.
贴满了全城的脚手架和地铁站
on every scaffolding and subway stop in the city.
顺便说一句 这侵权了
That's copyright infringement, by the way.
我当然在场
Of course I was there.
觉得怎么样？
So, what'd you think?
我觉得你的梅里特还得练练
I think your Merritt needs work.
- 我就说吧 - 别提这茬
- I knew it. - That's a sensitive topic.
- 你懂个屁 - 他在撒谎
- You don't even get it. - No. He's lying.
但整体设计令人印象深刻
But overall design was impressive.
我想你应该就是那个闷葫芦吧？
And that's you, I assume, the quiet guy?
- 典型的幕后推手 - 嗯 那个
- Textbook, behind the scenes. - Yeah, well,
- 亚历山大·赫尔曼… - 天啊
- Alexander Herrmann… - Oh, boy.
他说过 真正设计魔术的人
he said that the people who designed his tricks.
才是真正的天才
were the real geniuses.
既然你知道他的大名
The fact that you know that man's name,
显然你是“幕后”的
"behind the scenes" clearly.
而你 手法很高超 非常灵巧
And you, your sleight of hand was advanced. Good dexterity.
身手敏捷 真的 我很佩服
You're quick and nimble on your feet. Really, I was impressed.
- 谢谢 - 不客气
- Thanks. - You're welcome.
听起来我们挺棒的
Sounds like we're pretty great.
差得远呢
You're far from it.
不过 稍微调教一下 也许能成
But, uh, maybe with a little fine tuning, you could be.
我大概明白为什么“天眼”让我来找你们了
Yeah, I could… I could see why The Eye sent me to you.
- 抱歉 - 等等 你是说“天眼”？
- I'm sorry. - Wait, did you say "The Eye"?
对 天眼
Yeah, The Eye.
听好了
All right, listen.
三周前这张卡片寄到了我家
This card arrived at my apartment three weeks ago,
还有四张机票
along with four plane tickets.
夹层里藏着指令
and instructions hidden in the lining.
要完成一个
for a trick bigger and better.
前所未有的惊天魔术
than anything you have ever seen.
而且 居然指名要带上你们三个
A trick that, for some reason, includes the three of you.
- 我们？ - 嗯哼
- Us?Mm-hmm.
- 为什么不是其他骑士？ - 不
- Why not the other Horsemen? - No,
- 其他骑士都死透了 - 什么？
- the other horsemen are dead. - What?
对我来说 他们已经死透了 别打岔
To me, they're dead to me.Stop interrupting.
大家闹情绪 散伙了
No, things got emotional.Everyone quit.
我去澳洲流浪了一圈 说来话长
I took a walkabout in Australia.It's a long story.
所以现在你需要我们？
And now you need us?
卡片上是这么说的 对
According to that card, yes.
可我们不需要你 所以…
Well, we don't need you, so…
博斯科
Bosco.
干嘛？我们要这家伙干嘛？我们混得风生水起
What? What do we need this guy for? We're crushing it.
风生水起？
You're crushing it? You're stealing.
就偷那玩币小子一点钱？
a little money from some crypto bro.
我是说钓大鱼 老兄
I'm talking about big fish here, man.
我是说干一件
I'm talking about something that will.
真正能改变世界的大事
make a real difference.
我以为这才是你们的追求
I thought that's what you kids are all about.
确实是
It is. No, exactly.
我们的确是
Yes, we are.
对 但我觉得大鱼我们可以自己钓
Yeah, but I think we can catch our own fish.
你们行？不不 他…
You can?No, no, he…
- 祝你们好运 - 啥？别
Good luck with that. - What? No.
等等
Can you just wait one second?
你干嘛？这… 这是咋回事？
What are you doing? What's… what's going on?
你疯了吗？
Are you out of your mind?
- 这可是 J·丹尼尔·阿特拉斯 - 我知道他是谁
- This is J. Daniel Atlas. - Yeah, I know who he is.
他是个传奇
He's a freaking legend.
曾经是传奇 现在有点混蛋
He was a legend.Now he's just kind of a dick.
那个… 没问题
Can you…Yeah, sure.
博斯科 他确实混蛋 但他也是骑士
Bosco, he's kind of a dick, but he is a Horseman.
拜托 这次就信我们一回
I mean, come on, just trust us on this, please.
好了 做决定吧孩子们 怎么说？
Okay. Decision time, kids.What's it gonna be?
入局…
Are you in…
还是出局？
or are you out?
魔术怎么玩？
What's the trick?
南非 - 林波波
欢迎 尊贵的社区成员
Welcome, esteemed community members,
各位媒体朋友 亲友和同事们
valued press, friends and colleagues.
范德伯格集团
今晚我们欢聚一堂 共同庆祝
We are gathered here tonight to celebrate.
范德伯格集团
Vanderberg's latest and greatest mine,
最新最大的矿井 C3 也就是我们爱称的
C3, or as we like to call her,
“阿玛莱”祖鲁语意为“美丽之人”
"Amahle, " Zulu for "The Beautiful One."
因为在母亲眼中
Because every child is beautiful.
每个孩子都是美丽的
in the eyes of its mother.
我们的客户可以放心
Our customer can rest assured.
当你们购买这世上最伟大的爱之象征时
that when they buy the world's greatest symbol of love.
它是伴随着爱诞生的
that it was produced with nothing but.
敬阿玛莱 敬各位
To Amahle, and to all of you.
感谢大家远道而来
Well, thank you all so much for making the trip out here.
我想大家都对阿玛莱印象深刻
Now, I take it you were all impressed by Amahle.
抱歉 是 C3 矿井
Sorry, C3.
噢 真有戏剧性 哇 太神了
Oh, it's quite dramatic.Yeah, it's amazing.
我也知道你是特意挑了这个
But I also understand that you have chosen.
好日子来提意见的
this fine day to broach some concerns,
出乎你意料的是 我不介意
which, contrary to your expectations, I don't begrudge.
说吧
Fire away.
好吧 呃 董事会觉得
Right. Well, um, the board feels that.
预期可能太乐观了…
projections might be optimistic…
嗯
Mm.
随着人造钻石的竞争加剧
with increasing competition from lab grown.
万一贷款利率暴跌…
and, in the event borrowing rates plum…
威廉 威廉
William. William.
我父亲很欣赏你 但他管你叫
My father loved you, but there was.
“扫把星”是有原因的
a reason he called you his dark cloud.
噢 真遗憾
Aw, shame.
范德伯格家族从不失败
The Vanderberg family does not lose.
如你所知 我们的车队刚刚赢得了
As you're well aware, our motorsports team just won.
第七次摩纳哥锦标赛冠军
the Monaco Championship for the seventh time.
矿一定会出货
The mine will produce.
下一个？
Next?
好吧
Right.
定价 你设定的底价…
Pricing. The minimums that you've set for…
威廉 赏个脸
Will you humor me, William?
配合我不吝赐教一下？
In a demonstration about reality?
这颗钻石 大概 55 克拉？
This diamond is say, what, 55 carats?
安特卫普中心估价300 万美元
The AWDC would price it at 3, 000, 000 US dollars.
威廉 张开嘴
William, will you open your mouth.
把舌头伸出来
and stick out your tongue?
快点
Now.
- 认真的？ - 认真的
- Really? - Really.
如果威廉把它吞下去
Now, if William here were to swallow it,
这颗钻石会把他的喉咙割烂
that selfsame diamond would tear his throat to shreds.
救护车赶到前他就会失血而亡
He would bleed to death before paramedics arrived.
所以 对中心来说它值 300 万
So, to the AWDC, it's 3, 000, 000,
但对威廉来说 它是无价之宝
but to William, priceless.
那么告诉我 作为掌管着
Tell me then, as the CEO responsible.
世界最后几座大钻矿的 CEO
for the world's last great diamond mines,
我是该压低利润
should I undercut our profits,
还是定一个
or should I choose prices.
我知道那些特殊客户愿意付的价格？
that I know our unique clients will pay?
不出所料
As I thought.
现在…
Now…
除非还有其他问题
unless there are more concerns,
我要带着价目表去安特卫普了
I would like to head to Antwerp with my price list.
去炫耀一下我们的石头
and show off our stones.
呃 你知道你本来可以用
Oh, uh, you know, you probably could have led.
“免费欧洲游”来开场的？
with a free trip to Europe?
你们知道吗 关于安特卫普
You know, a little known fact.
有个冷知识…
about Antwerp is that…
太棒了 又是魔术冷知识 真有意思
Oh, great, more magic trivia. This is fun.
安特卫普 - 比利时
不 我只是想说
No, I was just gonna say that.
那里的饼干很好吃
they make great biscuits.
是吗？能给我们买点吗？
Oh, do they? Can we actually get some, please?
阿特拉斯买单 必须的 不
On Atlas, obviously.No.
不 我才不给你们买饼干
No, no, I'm not getting you biscuits.
我刚请你们吃了巧克力 行了吧？
I just got you chocolates, okay?
听着 这不是去度假
All right, listen, this is not a vacation, okay?
我们只有三天时间准备
We have three days to prepare an effect.
得设计出一个让你们那蹩脚的“佩珀尔幻象”
that'll make your barely passable Pepper's Ghost trick.
看起来像原始人涂鸦的效果
look like a cave painting.
过来
All right, come here.
海洋之心 史上最昂贵的宝石
The Heart Diamond, the most valuable jewel in history.
也是范德伯格矿业集团的基石
and the foundation of the Vanderberg Mining Corporation.
多年来 家族一直将这块巨石
Now, for years, the family's kept this big rock.
藏在秘密金库里
hidden inside their secret vault,
深埋地下 70 层
70 stories underground.
而且不在别处 就在阿拉伯沙漠
And not just any ground.The Arabian Desert.
除了亲信团队 无人涉足
No one beyond their most trusted team has been inside.
入口只有一部电梯
Access through a single elevator,
全天候武装守卫…
constantly monitored by armed guards…
身份验证通过
Identity verified.
背后还有
and behind a multi-level.
多层生物识别安保系统
biometric security system.
但全世界都将瞩目
But the world will be watching,
因为半个世纪以来 这是第一次
because for the first time in half a century,
这颗钻石被运到了这里
that diamond is being traveled here.
安特卫普 为了在这场私人拍卖会上
to Antwerp, to establish credibility.
给三天后即将拍卖的新货
and to spur bidding at a private auction.
树立信誉 刺激竞价
for the company's latest finds in three days' time.
好吧 偷东西我不介意
Okay, obviously, I'm down for stealing.
但这颗钻石有什么特别的？
But what makes this diamond so special?
因为神奇塔罗牌叫我们这么做 对吧 琼？
Well, because the magical tarot card told us to, June, right?
行行 挺逗的 能不能让我说完？
Yeah, okay, that's very cute.But can I please finish?
还没说完？天 你都说了半天了
You're not finished? Jeez, you've been talking forever.
对 我还要继续说
Yes, and I'm about to talk more.
所以 专心点
So, please, pay attention.
这几十年来 先是皮特·范德伯格
For decades, first, Peter Vanderberg,
现在是他女儿维罗妮卡
now his daughter, Veronika,
一直高价兜售这些钻石
have been selling these diamonds at inflated prices.
卖给世界各地的军火商 人贩子 军阀
to arms dealers, traffickers, warlords the world over,
帮他们洗钱
to, like, help launder their money.
也就是说 这些钱是脏的
So, I mean, the cash is dirty.
甚至可以说 是沾满鲜血的
I mean, in some cases, it's, like, literally blood-soaked.
然后 瞧…
But then, voila…
用这些宝石一换钱就洗白了
it's cleaned in exchange for these precious stones.
可以说 她简直是万恶之源
She makes all the world's worst people possible.
所以 不管是谁寄来了塔罗牌…
So, whoever sent that tarot card…
他们都是世上仅存的义士
Are the few truly honorable people left in this world.
唯一还在乎正义的人
The only people that still care about justice.
我已经很久没联系他们了
They're people I haven't spoken to in a long time.
他们自称“天眼”
They call themselves "The Eye, "
想要我们去做一件
and they want us to do something.
连四骑士都做不到的事
that the Horsemen never could.
伙计们
This, man,
这是个机会
this is a chance to drive a stake.
彻底干掉那个女魔头
through the heart of the devil herself.
干了
Let's do it.
今晚拍卖会上所有人都会盯着我
All eyes will be on me.
和那颗“海洋之心”
and the Heart tonight at the auction.
我必须光彩照人
I have to look dazzling.
有那个“小猫之吻”色号吗？
Do you have that Kitten Kiss color?
勒塔博
Lethabo.
在？ - 稻草人
Yes? - Straw.
那个《名利场》的英国摄影师是谁来着？
Who's that British photographer from Vanity Fair?
呃 叫什么名？马克…
Uh, what's his name again? Marc…
马克·斯克里伯？
Marc Scriber?
- 施赖伯 天啊 - 施赖伯
- Schreiber, good God. - Schreiber.
确认他的行程 取消其他的
Confirm him, cancel the others.
去年我们是广撒网 今年我们要搞“独家”
We went wide last year.This year, exclusivity.
好的 - 我们要开放 透明
All right. - We're open, transparent.
我们没什么可隐瞒的
We have nothing to hide.
好的 完美 我去办
Okay, perfect.I'll have it done.
我是维罗妮卡
This is Veronika.
♪ 嘘 小宝贝 ♪
♪ Hush little baby ♪
♪ 别说话 ♪
♪ Don't say a word ♪
你是谁？
Who is this?
♪ 爸爸给你买只模仿鸟 ♪
♪ Papa's gonna buy you a mocking bird ♪
♪ 如果那只模仿鸟 ♪
♪ And if that mocking bird ♪
出去
Vacate.
♪ 不唱歌 ♪
♪ Don't sing ♪
你怎么有这个号码？
How did you get this number?
♪ 爸爸给你买个大钻戒 ♪
♪ Papa's gonna buy you a diamond ring ♪
这是私人专线 而且你也太五音不全了
This is a private line, and that was a bit tone deaf.
我问你是谁
I asked who you are.
啊 维罗妮卡
Ah, Veronika.
你左边的储物柜
The storage unit to your left.
看着眼熟吗？
Look familiar?
这是 15 年前死去的那个男孩的
It belonged to that boy who died 15 years ago.
不管是对我还是对别人这都不算什么
This means nothing to me or anyone.
真的吗？
Really?
你我都很清楚你做了什么
You and I both know what you did.
听着 如果你有实锤
Look, if you have real evidence.
想搞垮我为什么不直接放出来？
and you're out to get me, why not just use it?
15 年前 你夺走了你父亲的最爱
Fifteen years ago, you took what your father loved most.
现在我要以牙还牙
Now I'm going to do the same to you.
我要海洋之心
I want the Heart Diamond.
你会把它交给我
You're going to give it to me.
否则我就竖起一面照妖镜
Or I'm going to hold up a looking glass.
让全世界看清你的真面目
for the whole world to see you as you are.
请便 我没什么可隐瞒的
Go ahead. I have nothing to hide.
马克·施赖伯
- 天啊 - 嘿
- Oh, my God. - Hey.
真不好意思
I'm so sorry about that.
免费拥抱
嗨 能帮我找找这个吗？
Hi. Can you help me find this?
我都找了一个小时了
I've been looking literally for an hour.
没问题 就在那边 女士
Yes. It's gonna be right over there, ma'am.
马克·施赖伯 我是詹姆斯·温 范德伯格公关部的
Marc Schreiber, James Winn, Vanderberg PR.
久仰大名
Huge admirer of your work.
詹姆斯？丹妮去哪了？
James? What happened to Dani?
噢 丹妮啊 很遗憾 我们不得不解雇了她
Oh, Dani. Yeah, sadly, we had to let her go.
原来她有种族歧视倾向
Turns out she was racist.
而且 她居然给你订了雷迪森蓝标酒店
And also, she booked you into the Radisson Blu.
- 还是视野不佳的双人间 - 呃
- in a partial view, double. - Ugh.
幸好我自作主张帮你换到了 FRANQ 酒店
Thankfully, I took the liberty of moving you to the FRANQ.
我超爱 FRANQ
I do love the FRANQ.
是的 只有总统套房才配得上总统
Yes, the presidential suite is befitting of, well,
以及像您这样才华横溢的摄影师
presidents and talented photographers like yourself.
呃 您的晚宴邀请函已经改寄了
Uh, your gala invitation has been rerouted.
能让我确认一下您的预订信息吗？
If I could just check your confirmation?
谢谢
Thank you.
我还把您的拍摄时间从 7 点推到了 9 点
I also bumped your shoot from 7:00 to 9:00 p.m.
好让您有充足的时间施展您的魔法
to give you proper time to make your magic.
- 终于有个懂行的了 - 没错
- Someone gets it. - Yeah.
安特卫普
♪ Diamond - Angelina Jordan ♪
♪ 我像超新星一样闪耀 ♪
♪ I'm shinin' like a supernova ♪
♪ 高举双手敞开心扉… ♪
♪ With my hands up high And my heart wide open… ♪
♪ 我像钻石一样更加璀璨 ♪
♪ I shine even more bright Like a diamond ♪
♪ 将恐惧从肩头拂去… ♪
♪ Brush that fear right off my shoulder… ♪
就拿实验室培育的钻石来说吧
Take, for instance, diamonds created in laboratories.
号称有价值
They purport to have value,
但既不天然也不稀有
but they're neither natural nor rare.
哪个诚实的女人希望手指上戴着个谎言呢？
What honest woman wants a falsehood on her finger?
我同意
I agree.
世间仅存的伟大真理之一
One of the great truths left.
就是天然宝石所蕴含的力量
is the power behind a natural gem.
真正的钻石能让人充满激情
Real diamonds fill people with passion,
这几个世纪以来皆是如此
as they have for centuries.
没错 事实上 玛丽·安托瓦内特
That's right.In fact, Marie-Antoinette,
只戴了一天“希望蓝钻”
wore the Hope Diamond for a single day,
一个月后…
and a month later…
就被推上了断头台
was dragged to the guillotine.
被一群 嗯 如你所说 充满激情的人
by some very, well, as you say, passionate folks.
玛丽·安托瓦内特不是死于钻石
Marie-Antoinette didn't die because of a diamond.
而是死于极度缺乏同理心
She died because of a monstrous lack of empathy.
那个…
Well…
其实 她从未戴过那颗钻
And truth is, she never even wore the Hope.
只是人们相信她戴过
People just believe she did.
是吗？这倒挺有意思
Really?That's kind of interesting.
所以杀她的不是暴民
So it was not the mob that killed her,
也不是断头台
and it was not the guillotine,
而是一个… 故事
it was a… a story.
看来我对自己请的人不太了解
I must not know my own guest list.
你是做钻石生意的？
Are you in the diamond business?
不不 我和你一样 是做“幻觉”生意的
No, no, I'm in the illusion business, like you.
看 几百年来 钻石一文不值
See, for centuries, diamonds were worthless.
直到像维罗妮卡这样极度聪明富有的人
until some very smart, very rich people.
告诉我们这些小小的玻璃碴子
like Veronika here, told us that, not only.
不仅稀有
are these little shards of glass rare,
而且任何有自尊的情侣
but that no self-respecting couple.
结婚时都必须得来一颗
could possibly get married without one.
不 这才是真正的高明魔术
No, now, that one is a good magic trick.
但这个魔术的问题是…
The problem with the trick is, um…
所有好戏最后都有个意想不到的反转
All the good ones have a little twist in the tale.
是你吗？
Is it you?
什么是我？
Is what me?
- 当然不是 - 不不
- Of course not. - No, no.
我是说 我要不像你的其他客人那样
I mean, you wouldn't have let me in had I not demonstrated.
展现出极高的道德水准 你也不会放我进来
the finest moral fiber, like some of your other guests.
那边那位是军火商路易斯·布里塞尼奥吧
I notice Luis Briseño, the arms dealer over there.
幸会
Hello, sir.
当然还有玛丽亚·博特尼克
And of course, Maria Bortnick, when starstruck,
一边从容交际一边垄断着官方媒体
how she manages to mingle while monopolizing her state media.
也许你也愿意表明身份
Perhaps you'd care to reveal yourself.
这样我们也能好好审视一下你
Then we can apply the same scrutiny to you.
- 嗯哼
Hmm.
别急嘛
Not just yet.
抱歉打断了
I'm sorry for interrupting.
没必要
That won't be necessary.
随他去吧
Let him eat cake.
马克·施赖伯
Marc Schreiber.
维罗妮卡·范德伯格
Veronika Vanderberg.
我们速战速决 好吗？
Let's make this quick, shall we?
拍卖会马上开始了
Our auction begins shortly.
相信你会把我和海洋之心拍得完美
I trust you can do me and the Heart justice.
是的 但我有个规矩 那就是我说了算
Yes. I only have one rule.What I say goes.
好吧 我相信我能找到温顺的一面
Well, I'm sure I can find my submissive side.
如果你找不到我会帮你找
Well, if not, I'll find it for you.
噢 我喜欢你
Ooh. I like you.
这边请 亲爱的
Right this way, darling.
别太哑光了 好的好的
I don't want to be too matte.Sure. Sure, sure.
我不喜欢鼻翼发亮
And I don't like the sides of my nose shining.
明白
Okay.
- 给我看看 - 嗯
- Show me. - Mm-hmm.
不好意思 镜头里这只小苍蝇
Excuse me, can the little fruit fly.
能不能请你走开 走开 走开？
in my shot please shoo, shoo, shoo?
谢谢
Thank you.
唯一比那颗钻石更值钱的就是我的时间
The only thing more valuable than that diamond is my time.
我调查过你
I did my research on you.
你的行业和我的行业一样
Your industry, like mine,
都充斥着人造的传说
is besieged by manufacturer lore.
但你 你展现的是真实之美
But you, you bring us beauty as it is.
这点我们很像
We're alike in that regard.
我们不卖弄虚假 我们贩卖真实
We don't sell contrivance, we sell reality.
我觉得 我们根本不用卖
Well, I would argue that we don't sell at all.
别人抢着买
Others buy.
哼
Hmm.
让我看看…
Let's see…
呃… 那个钻石 拿出来
Uh… The diamond, take it out.
没门 小子
Nah, boy.
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
玻璃反光会毁了照片
The glare in the glass will mar the photos.
我无法容忍瑕疵
I don't tolerate imperfections.
我想像范德伯格女士
I don't imagine someone as ravishing.
这样迷人的人也不会容忍
as Ms. Vanderberg does either.
所以 要么拿出来要么另请高明
So, take it out or find yourself a new photographer.
其实 我就等你这句话呢
In truth, I was hoping you'd ask.
我不记得我有说过
I don't remember asking.
这就对了
There it is.
美极了 保持住 太棒了
Beautiful. Work it. Fabulous.
太棒了 完美
Fabulous. Fabulous.
美
Beautiful.
对 微笑 享受
Yes. Smiling, we're having fun.
这就是我们想要的效果
This is what we came for.
别动 别动
Hold it, hold it.
这就是我要的大片
That's the money shot.
别动
Hold it.
还有你 女士 离远点
And you, ma'am, are far enough.
我只是想… 想帮忙
I'm just trying…I'm trying to help.
她脑门比那钻石还亮
Her forehead is shinier than the diamond.
实际上 我在做我的工作 我不听你指挥
Actually, I'm doing my job.I don't take orders from you.
只要事关海洋之心你就得听我的
When it comes to the Heart, you listen to me.
- 出去 - 我… 我自己会走
- Get out. - I… I can walk myself.
- 谢谢 - 好吧
- Thank you. - Right.
施赖伯先生
Mr. Schreiber.
如果你真如你所说的那么厉害
If you're all you purport to be,
你应该已经拍到你想要的了
you should already have what you need.
- 绰绰有余 谢谢 - 很好
- More than enough. Thank you. - Excellent.
合作愉快 但我还有买家在等着
Well, it's been a pleasure, but I have buyers waiting.
我受够了 受够了这帮人胡闹
I've had enough of this of this nonsense.
确保存放安全
Make sure it's secured.
好的 勒塔博
Yes, Lethabo.
- 搞什么 怎么回事？ - 不知道 我不知道
- What the hell, what happened? - I don't know. I don't know.
没时间了 走
Time's ticking. Let's go.
终于 万众期待的拍卖会开始了
At last, the auction we've all been waiting for.
今晚能坐在这里的各位
Now, if you're here tonight,
大概觉得自己什么世面都见过了
you probably think you've seen everything.
所以我要问问你们…
So it is to you that I ask…
真的见过一切吗？
Everything?
这颗钻石已经 25 年未曾现世
It's not been seen in person for a quarter of a century.
至今仍是史上最大的钻石 海洋之心
Still the largest diamond ever discovered, the Heart.
恭喜各位
Congratulations to all of you.
居然逍遥法外了这么久
and for getting away with it for so long.
猜怎么着？
Well, guess what?
气候变化
Climate change.
也不相信你们
doesn't believe in you, either.
你们从地球母亲身上榨取财富
You tore your fortunes from our Mother Earth,
坐着私人飞机 烧毁她的天空…
set fire to her skies in your private jets…
- 行了 她懂了 - 对对对
- Okay, she gets it. - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
用你们无尽的贪婪把她榨干…
Bled her dry with your insatiable…
年轻人 我们都想拯救世界
Young man, we all want to save the world here,
但时间宝贵 你正在浪费我的时间
but time is also precious and you're wasting mine.
闭嘴吧 闪光女
Zip it, sparkles.
别再用
Why don't you stop sucking.
塑料吸管吸溜了 吸这个吧
on plastic straws, and suck on this!
尊贵的客人们 我是 J·丹尼尔·阿特拉斯
Honored guests.My name is J. Daniel Atlas.
作为魔术四骑士中你们最爱的一位
You may remember me as your personal favorite.
大家应该还记得我吧
of the Four Horsemen of magic.
看仔细了
Now watch closely.
我要让那颗着名的海洋之心 出现在我手心
as I make the famous Heart Diamond appear on my palm.
天哪 他和绿色和平组织一样
Gee-whiz, he must be as starved.
缺爱缺关注啊
for attention as Greenpeace here.
放心 钻石非常安全
Rest assured that the diamond is completely safe.
是吗？
Is it?
一位智者曾告诉我 其实就是对着镜子说的
Now, a wise man once told me, in the mirror, in fact,
永远别自以为你是屋里最聪明的人
uh, never assume you're the smartest person in the room,
证明它
prove it.
请便
Be my guest.
好 那就看看 能不能把这柜子打开
All right, well, let's see if we can get that case open.
呃… 阿布拉卡达布拉
Uh… Abracadabra.
呵 没开 呃… 急急如律令
Huh. Nope. Uh… Alakazam.
等等
Wait.
芝麻开门
Open sesame.
- 啊哈
Ah.
在我这儿依然安全
Still safe with me.
不 放松 嗯 放松 维罗妮卡
No. Relax. Mm, relax, Veronika.
正如你的广告词所说
Now, as your ads like to remind us,
钻石恒久远
diamonds are forever.
- 护送她离开 快 - 拦住他 拦住他
- Get her to safety. Now!-You stop him! Stop him!
拦住他
Stop him!
- 杰克-嘿
Jack. - Hey.
- 你怎么在这儿？ - 救你的命
- What are you doing here? - Saving your ass.
- 啊-不客气
Ah. - You're welcome.
你也收到卡片了 呵
You got one, too. Huh.
- 嗨 我是琼 - 是啊
- Hi. I'm June. - Yeah.
她是谁？抱歉 自己人
Who's she? Sorry, she's with us.
钻石在哪儿？
Where is the diamond?
什么？
What?
看来你们根本不关心环境
I guess you guys don't care about the environment.
你比看起来强壮多了
You're stronger than you look.
嘿
Hey!
快跑
Run away.
保安：嘿 嘿 嘿
SECURITY GUARD: Hey! Hey, hey!
站住 别让他们跑了
Stop! Don't let them get away!
好吧 现在咋办？
Okay, what now?
我的卡片只说把你弄出来 我也不知道
My card just said to get you out of there. I don't know.
亨利·里维斯？
Henley Reeves?
我贴了好多你的海报
I have so many posters of you.
- 你是我童年的… - 行了 追星的事稍后再说
- You're my childhood… - All right, fanboy later.
不过… 见到你真好
But it does, uh… You know, it is really nice to see you.
回头再追星 我们得走了
Fanboy later. We got to go up.
举起手来 不许动
Put your hands up and don't move!
真扯淡
This is some bullshit.
搞什么鬼？
What is happening?
贝多芬 D 大调协奏曲
Beethoven's Concerto in D major.
扯淡 扯淡 真扯淡
Bullshit, bullshit, bullshit!
哇哦 梅里特？那是什么鬼？
Whoa. Merritt? What…What the hell was that?
阿特拉斯 我想看你
Atlas, I would like to see you.
用“比利时语”催眠三个大汉
hypnotize three dudes in Belgian.
你是说弗拉芒语
You mean Flemish.
行 这就说得通了
Okay, that explains it.
感人的重逢 该走了
Lovely reunion. We have to go.
亨利·里维斯
Henley Reeves!
- 欢迎归队 - 谢谢
- Welcome back!-Thanks.
容我说一句 你真是…
And may I say, you are…
- 好了 快走快走 - 对对对 走走走
- Okay, come on, let's go!-Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
我只是想夸夸她
I was paying her a compliment.
因为见到她很高兴 仅此而已
because it was nice to see her, and only her.
- 我只是… - 知道了
- I was… - We get it!
在上面
Up there.
哇 哇 是来接我们的？
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!Is that for us?
你看到还有别人在逃命吗？
Do you see any other people trying to escape?
快点 快点 走
Come on, come on. Go, go!
快 快
Come on, come on.
呃 一直在我也手里
Uh, it was in my hand.
从没…
the whole time. It never…
他们没换钻石
They didn't swap the diamond.
他们换的是箱子
They swapped the case.
而你 女士 离远点
And you, ma'am, are far enough.
别再用塑料吸管吸溜了
Why don't you stop sucking on plastic straws,
吸这个吧
and suck on this!
尊贵的客人们…
Honored guests…
芝麻开门
Open sesame.
在我这很安全
Still safe with me.
钻石恒久远
Diamonds are forever.
- 勒塔博 - 在 夫人？
- Lethabo. - Yes, ma'am?
我们要让他们后悔
We're going to make them regret this.
加倍后悔
And then some.
马克·施赖伯 《名利场》
Marc Schreiber, Vanity Fair.
我错过什么了吗？
What did I miss?
话说 我还以为会更闪呢
You know, I thought it'd be shinier.
行了 还给我
Okay.All right, give it back.
- 你干嘛？ - 噢 抱歉 太滑了
- What are you doing? - Oh. Sorry. It's so slippery.
- 喂 喂 - 小心点
- Hey. Hey. - Heads up.
别再那样了
Okay, don't do that again.
那个 我能问问 这帮小屁孩是谁吗？
Hey, can I address the, uh, infant in the room?
呃… 他们是谁？
Uh… Who are these guys?
就是这群好孩子用 AI 换脸伪造了我们的演出
These are the wonderful kids that deepfaked our show.
啥？ 是啊
What? Yeah.
就是你们害得警察冲进我家的？
You had the cops sent to my house?
- 你们吓坏我孩子了 - 呃 抱歉
- You freaked out my kids. - Yeah, sorry.
- 真对不起 - 抱歉啊
- Sorry about that. - Sorry about that.
孩子们怎么样？
How are the kids, though?
你为了它抛弃我们的无聊郊区生活过得还好吗？
How is the whole boring suburban life you left us for?
嘿 别这样 你错过了机会
Hey, relax, man.You missed your shot.
- 哼 - 看到那颗钻多大没？
Hmm. - See the size of that rock?
拿来我看看
No, let me see that.
虽然不是海洋之心但也挺惊人
Ooh, it's no Heart Diamond, but it's impressive.
我早告诉你了 丹尼
I already told you, Danny.I didn't feel safe.
让我挺着六个月大肚子
trying to escape from a straitjacket.
倒吊着穿束身衣
hanging upside down.
- 我觉得不安全 - 至于嘛
- I was six months pregnant. - Come on.
最后我们会把你翻过来的
We would have flipped you right side up at the end.
没事的
You'd have been fine.
- 别这样 - 你们根本没想我
- Come on. - You guys didn't even miss me.
你们找替补花了好久？一下午？
How long did it take you to replace me? An afternoon?
呃 确切说 是大半个晚上
Um, and the better part of an evening.
哎 说到这 露拉呢？
Hey, speaking of, how is Lula?
- 你们俩还… - 没
- Are you guys still, uh… - No.
她… 她搬去巴黎了
She, uh… she moved to Paris.
不是吧 她甩了伟大的 J·怀尔德？天啊
Oh, no. She dumped the great J. Wilder. My God.
真遗憾 节哀
I'm sorry. My apologies.
你现在不该在
Don't you need to be on some, like,
某艘游轮上丢人现眼吗？
cruise ship somewhere humiliating yourself?
- 丢人现眼？ - 是啊
- Humiliating myself? - Yeah.
我每趟游轮赚五位数外加福利
I make five figures per cruise, plus perks.
“外加福利”他说“外加福利”
"Plus perks."He said, "plus perks."
我还以为梅里特
And I thought Merritt drinking himself.
在墨西哥酗酒等死已经够惨了
to death in Mexico was depressing. Ooh.
说到这个 我还得继续喝呢
Speaking of, I got to get back to it.
这肝可不会自己喝废
This liver's not gonna destroy itself.
呃 能让这玩意靠岸吗？
Uh, can we dry dock this thing?
等等 你要走了？
Wait, wait, wait.You're leaving?
是啊 叙旧很愉快
Well, yeah, I mean, great catching up.
下一个十年再见？
Um, I don't know, what, see you in another ten?
很高兴认识你们 小蝌蚪们
Nice to meet you, little tadpoles.
再见
Adios.
知道吗？我也要撤了
Yeah, you know what?I'm out of here, too.
我还有场演出要赶
I have a gig to get to.
真的？他们给你报销打车费吗？
Really?They're covering your Uber?
签了保密协议 无可奉告
Signed an NDA. Can't say a word.
你干什么？
What are you doing?
六个把手没一个能打开这破门
Six handles and none of them open it.
你以为在跟谁说话？让开
Who do you think you're talking to? Move.
抱歉 我不太清楚
I'm sorry, but I don't really know.
你们之间发生了什么
what's going on with you guys.
但我感觉这儿有很多奇怪的历史遗留问题
I'm getting the feeling there's a lot of weird history here,
气氛有点尴尬
and things are a little awkward.
是啊 你们曾经是四骑士啊
Yeah, you guys, you used to be the Horsemen.
我不明白你们为什么要解散？
I don't get it.Why did you break up?
问他们 问问他们为什么解散
Ask them.Ask them why we broke up.
如果我能做主 我们根本不会散
If it was up to me, we wouldn't have.
- 天眼想让我们… - 不 不是
- The Eye wanted us to… - No, no.
揭露一个俄罗斯军火商
expose a Russian arms dealer.
我们非得再揭一遍伤疤吗？
Do we really have to live through this again?
我们犯了些大错 我们变得…
We made some huge mistakes, we got…
- 散漫 - 自大
- Sloppy. - Cocky.
因为我们 迪伦·施莱克再也无法
Because of us, Dylan Shrike will never see.
走出俄罗斯监狱了
the outside of a Russian prison again.
- 谁？ - 迪伦·施莱克 行了吧？
- Who? - Dylan Shrike. Okay?
他也是骑士 拜托 做做功课吧 老兄
He's a Horseman. Come on.Do your homework, man.
真抱歉 各位 我真不知道
I'm so sorry.Guys, I had no idea.
什么 他被永远关在里面了？
What, he's stuck in there forever?
这显然是个悲剧
Which is obviously a tragedy.
我也永远无法原谅自己
and something I'll never forgive myself for.
- 我也一样 行吧 各位
- Nor will I. - Yeah, fine, man.
但这不意味着你们就得不干了啊
But it didn't mean you have to quit.
天啊 这真是…
Man, that is, uh…
真扫兴 各位 抱歉啊
It's really a bummer, guys.Sorry about that.
“扫兴”？
"A bummer"?
我… 我真是爱死
I… I… I love the way.
你们这代人那种言简意赅的总结方式了
your generation sums things up so eloquently.
谁能给我解释一下
I mean, someone explain to me.
为什么这帮没长毛的小孩会在这儿？
why these pre-pubes are even here.
和你一样 老兄
Same reason you are, man.
天眼选的
The Eye wanted 'em.
好了 海洋之心到手了
Well, we got the Heart.
天眼接下来想让我们干嘛？
What does The Eye want us to do next?
- 不知道 - 我只知道一件事
- No idea. - I know one thing.
你们手里拿着价值五亿美金的钻石
You've got a half a billion dollar diamond in your hands.
- 他们会联系我们的 - 是啊 可能吧
- They're gonna get in touch. - Yeah, probably.
等等 等等 阿特拉斯 能看看你的卡吗？
Whoa, wait, wait.Atlas, can I see your card?
给
Yeah.
- 嗯哼
Hmm.
- 哇哦 - 是张地图
- Whoa. - It's a map.
- 嘿 阿特拉斯 是你爸 - 不 这是…
- Hey, Atlas, it's your dad. - No, it's…
只有四骑士聚齐才会显现的地图
It's a map that only reveals itself when the Horsemen are together.
想得美 真的吗 哥们？
Fat chance.Really, dude?
拜托
I mean, come on,
天眼显然想让你们一起干这票
The Eye obviously wants you guys to do this.
你们是四骑士 拿出点骑士的样子来
You're the Horsemen.Start acting like it.
行吧
All right.
我想罗萨里托可以再等几天
I suppose Rosarito can wait a couple days.
我… 我可以试着改一下演出时间
I… I can try to reschedule this gig.
不太容易 但我会搞定的
It's not gonna be easy, but I'll figure it out.
说真的 我还真有点怀念
I mean, I have kind of missed running for my life.
跟你们一起亡命天涯跳屋顶的日子
and jumping off roofs with you guys.
- 欢迎归队 - 谢谢
- It's good to have you back. - Thanks.
好 这是哪儿？
Okay, so where is this place?
法国 - 鲁西永城堡
我们来这儿干嘛？
What are we supposed to be doing here?
天眼会告诉我们的
The Eye will let us know.
- 好了 拍照时间 - 你干嘛？
- All right, picture time. - What are you doing?
拍照啊 现在情侣都这样
Taking a photo.That's what couples do now.
请别把绝密地点的照片
Please don't post photos.
发到网上 别嫉妒
of the top secret location.Don't be jealous.
我知道你想入镜
I know you want to be in it.
是啊 我还真不想入镜
Yeah.I don't want to be in it.
因为这会被当成… 回忆
Because it can be used for…For memories.
不 不是回忆 是呈堂证供
No, not memories.Evidence.
呵 我从没见过这种门
Huh. I've never seen a door like this.
好吧 我打不开
Okay, I can't open it.
杰克 你来？
You got this, Jack?
等等 你是说“琼”吧？
Wait. Don't you mean "June"?
- 杰克是我们的开锁专家 - 哇哦
- Jack's our lockpick. - Whoa.
看起来有点良性竞争的意思
Looks like a little healthy competish.
拜托 这不公平
Come on, this isn't fair.
我开锁的时候她还没出生呢
I've been picking locks since before she was born.
我找找锁眼
Let me find the keyhole.
也许在那边 在下面
Maybe the other side.Yeah, it's underneath.
你现在这样可没什么说服力啊 杰克
You're not inspiring confidence right now, Jack.
他行的 嗯哼
He's got it.Hmm.
- 他行的 - 手生了？
- He's got it. - Feeling rusty?
别催我
Don't rush me.
他什么时候开始开锁啊？
When does he start the lock picking?
嘿 杰克 我觉得这锁不是用来撬的
Hey, Jack, I don't think this is a lock you pick.
是用来解的 所以…
I think it's a lock you solve. So…
给他露一手
Show him how it's done.
哇哦
Whoa.
介意我快速搞定这个吗？
Do you mind if I just figure this out real quickly?
好了
Okay.
如果你玩过密室逃脱
If you've ever done an escape room,
就知道会有各种谜题
you'd know there are all kinds of different puzzles.
不仅仅是锁和钥匙
It's not just about locks and keys.
哇哦 呵
Whoa. Huh.
你该更新下技能库了 杰克
You might want to update your game, Jack.
哇哦
Whoa.
那请吧 带路
But, by all means, lead the way.
我觉得最后那下还是他松开的
I think he loosened it for her, ultimately.
- 呵 - 噢
- Huh. - Ooh.
- 哇哦 - 哇
- Whoa. - Wow.
呃 这是什么地方？
Uh, what is this place?
魔术宅男的天堂
Magic nerd heaven.
P T 塞尔比特的棺材？
P.T. Selbit's coffin?
看见没？
See?
各位 胡迪尼的束身衣
Guys, Houdini's straitjacket.
没错
Yes, it is.
嘿 看在往日情分上我能把你塞进去吗？
Hey, can I put you in here for old time's sake?
- 不要 - 不要？
- No. - No?
我觉得挺好玩的啊
I thought it was funny.
多谢夸奖 你想进去吗？
Thanks a lot. You wanna come in?
- 不想 - 那就是了
- No. - Right.
查理 快看这个 哥们
Charlie, check this out, dude.
是什么？
What is it?
徒手接子弹
Bullet catch.
不会吧
No way!
哟
Yo!
- 死胡同？ - 对 死胡同
- Dead end? - Yeah, dead end.
嘿 各位 死路一条
Hey, guys, dead end.
- 真的吗？ - 嗯哼
- Or, is it? - Hmm.
天啊
Oh, my God.
没错 确实是
Yeah, it is.
嗯 真奇怪
Hmm, that's weird.
骰子应该在这里球应该在这里
The die should be here and the ball should be here.
- 哇哦 - 干得漂亮
- Whoa. - Well played.
小意思
It's nothing.
四行
Four rows.
1 5 8 4？是密码吗？
One, five, eight, four?Is it a code?
- 1 1 5 6 18… - 减去 4
- One, one, five, six, 18… - Minus four.
- 1 8 9？-15 84-
One, eight, nine? - Fifteen, eighty-four.
- 什… - 1584
- 1584. - Wha…
《妖术的发现》
The Discoverie of Witchcraft.
第一本关于舞台魔术的书
It's the first book on stage magic.
那是它的出版年份
It's when it was published.
天 他怎么知道的？
God, how does he know that?
呃 他基本上就是台装满无用知识的电脑
Uh, he's basically a computer full of useless information.
呵
Huh.
“无用”？
"Useless"?
真酷
This is cool.
- 不可思议 - 漂亮
- Unreal. - Nice.
嘿 各位 是古堡的平面图
Hey, guys, it's the floor plan of the chateau.
但有些不一样
But it's different somehow.
颠倒乾坤
Up is down.
左右互搏
Left is right.
连房间都是障眼法
Even the rooms are tricks.
我的骑士们
My Horsemen.
萨迪厄斯
Thaddeus!
- 见到你真好 - 见到你们真好 亲爱的
- So good to see you. - So good to see you, darling.
你明明可以看下可视门铃然后给我们开门的
You could've just checked the Ring camera and buzzed us in.
那多没意思啊
Now, where's the fun in that?
先生 嗨 我是查理
Sir. Hi, I'm Charlie.
- 我是你的超级粉丝 - 嗨 查理
- I'm such a big fan of yours. - Hi, Charlie.
呃…
Um…
我从没亲眼见过这么大的鲁伯透镜
I've never seen a Lubor Lens this big in person.
真的？那你见识的还在后头呢
Really? Well, you ain't seen nothing yet.
所以是你寄的塔罗牌？
So you sent the tarot cards?
不
No.
不 我早就不干这种蠢事了
No, I've long since given up such foolishness,
也不管你们这摊子烂事了
and your collective dysfunction.
不 我现在只给我的
No, the only magic I do nowadays.
孙子孙女变魔术
is for my grandchildren.
不过 几周前
Some weeks ago, however,
确实有张卡片出现在我家门口
a card did appear on my doorstep,
警告我把古堡准备好
warning me to prepare this chateau.
迎接七位即将亡命天涯的
for the arrival of seven soon-to-be fugitives.
通缉犯
from the law.
- 这很合理 - 是啊
- That tracks. - Yeah.
等等 天眼为什么要我们来这？
Wait, so why does The Eye want us here?
嗯 我只能假设无论他们
Well, I can only assume that whatever it is.
接下来想让你们做什么
they want you to do next.
线索都藏在这些墙里
is hidden somewhere in these walls.
看 这座古堡 鲁西永古堡
See, this chateau, Chateau Roussillon,
曾是他们的家
used to be their home.
1943 年
In 1943,
盟军急需各种军事奇迹
the Allies needed military miracles from every source.
他们招募了当时
They enlisted the aid.
最有才华的一批魔术师
of some of the most talented magicians of the time.
他们用泥巴 纸板 灯光
They built a whole city using mud, cardboard, lights,
还有数千个充气橡胶坦克造了一整座假城
thousands of inflatable rubber tanks.
用来迷惑德军
to misdirect the Germans.
贾斯帕·马斯基林的杰作
The genius of Jasper Maskelyne.
看来有人很懂历史
Somebody knows his history.
等等 那纳粹和这钻石有什么关系？
Wait, so, what do the Nazis have to do with the diamond?
这个 我不知道
That, I do not know.
但答案一定就在这儿
But the answer is here somewhere.
我们找找看吧
We just have to start looking.
范德伯格女士 范德伯格女士
Ms. Vanderberg.Ms. Vanderberg.
有传言说您的公司
How do you respond to the rumors that your company.
不过是个洗钱的幌子 您怎么回应？
is nothing but a front for money laundering?
四骑士就是一群
The Horsemen are thieves.
伪装成反资本主义艺人的小偷
posing as anti-capitalist entertainers,
他们不公正地针对我和我的公司
and they have unfairly targeted me and my good company.
我挑战任何诽谤我们的人
I challenge anyone who maligns us to look.
去仔细查我们的运营和帐目
closely at our operations and our books.
我也挑战警方把那些魔术师
And I challenge police to put those magicians.
送回他们该去的地方 过去的历史里
back where they belong, in the past.
好了 无可奉告
All right, no more questions.
别再问了 拜托 谢谢
No more questions, please!Thank you!
国际刑警说这是内鬼干的
Interpol said it was an inside job.
窃贼确切地知道盲点在哪儿
Thieves knew exactly where the blind spots were.
感觉如何？ - 让我猜猜
How was it? - Let me guess.
就是你在背后指使四骑士
You're the one behind these Horsemen.
和那群小马夫的吧
and their little stable hands.
不 我为什么要向你讨要钻石
No. Why would I ask for the diamond.
然后再去偷它？
and then try to steal it?
如果我是你 我会想办法
If I were you, I'd figure out a way.
把它拿回来 越快越好
to get it back, and fast.
我知道你和你的车队
I understand that you and your race team.
这周晚些时候会去阿布扎比
will be in Abu Dhabi later this week.
完美的中间地带
A perfect neutral ground.
我会带上证据
I'll bring my evidence.
你带上你的“海洋之心”如果你还有心的话
You bring your Heart, if you have one.
我…
I…
- 找到他们了吗？ - 我们有几条线索
- Have you found them yet? - We do have a few leads.
有人看见他们往南出了比利时
They were seen headed south out of Belgium.
现在的消息是
Now they're saying the Horsemen.
一小时前有人在法国看见了四骑士
have been seen in France one hour ago.
法国警长欠我个人情
The head of the French police owes me.
打给他 就说我要四骑士的项上人头
Just call him and say that I want these Horsemen's heads.
端在盘子里给我送来
served up on a platter.
宪兵队会找到他们的 我确信
The gendarme will find them.I'm sure of it.
萨迪厄斯让我们找东西
Thaddeus told us to look for something.
你觉得是什么？
What do you think it is?
噢 哇 真酷
Oh, wow. This is cool.
你话不多啊
You are not a big talker.
噢 抱歉
Oh. Sorry.
但你道歉倒是挺勤快
But you are a big apologizer.
抱歉 我又来了
Sorry. I just did it again.
抱歉 我是说… 我只是紧张
Sorry. I mean…I'm just nervous.
我是你们的超级粉丝
I'm a big fan of you guys.
我还把警察招来了 我真的…
And I got the cops called in, and I'm really…
我真的… 我不说了
I'm really…I'm not gonna say it.
没事了
You're forgiven.
而且你们让四骑士看起来很风光
And you guys made the Horsemen look good.
但我没看见你 你为什么没出镜？
But I didn't see you.Why weren't you in it?
噢 我只是… 我更喜欢幕后 你知道的
Oh, I just… I prefer to be behind the scenes, you know.
魔术都是我设计的
I design all of our tricks.
呃 我们在哪儿？感觉迷路了
Um, where are we going?I feel like we're lost.
你是真的喜欢幕后
Do you really prefer that,
还是拿它当挡箭牌？
or is that just something you hide behind?
呃 什么意思？
Uh, what do you mean?
嗯 我… 哇哦
Well, I… Whoa.
多年来 我告诉自己我想当助手
For years, I told myself I wanted to be an assistant,
我不介意被阿特拉斯抢风头
that I didn't mind being upstaged by Atlas,
因为他太才华横溢了
'cause he's so brilliant.
但其实 我只是… 我害怕
But really, I just…I was afraid.
我害怕站在聚光灯下
I was afraid to take the spotlight.
噢 萨迪厄斯是对的 颠倒乾坤
Ooh. Thaddeus was right.Up is down.
颠倒屋 酷
Upside down room. Cool.
酷？
Cool?
你就没点惊叹的感觉吗？
Is nothing impressive to you?
所以我才说“酷”啊
That's why I said "cool."
你不懂“酷”是啥意思吗？
Do you not know what cool means?
行了 咱们还是研究下
All right, let's just try to figure out.
这房间怎么回事吧 行吗？
how this room works, okay?
好
Yeah.
搞定了
Figured it out.
当然 没错 你什么都知道了
Of course. That's right.You know everything already.
这回我又做错什么了？
So what did I do wrong this time?
啊 没有 抱歉
Ah, nothing. My apologies.
你很厉害 看你解谜是种荣幸
You're amazing.It's an honor to watch you.
有没有人说过你是个控制狂？
Has anyone ever told you that you're a control freak?
有 好多次
Yep. Many times.
哇 嘿
Whoa! Hey!
我还真搞定了
I did figure it out.
哇哦 哇
Whoa. Wow.
软糖劲儿上来了
Gummies kicked in.
我在想我们要找什么
I wonder what we're looking for.
任何奇怪的东西
Anything weird.
这儿哪样不奇怪 天
This is all weird. Jesus.
看这个
Look at this.
知道吗 我以前一直很崇拜你
You know, I have always looked up to you.
噢 是吗？
Oh, yeah?
对 在你变成游轮魔术师之前
Yeah, before you became a cruise ship magician.
嘿 我也接企业活动的
Hey, I also do corporate events.
噢 不会吧 看不出来
Oh, no way. I couldn't tell.
真是白忙活 现在咋办？
So that was a total waste. What now?
一个魔术 行吗？别整花活
One trick. Okay? No charm,
别耍嘴皮子 就一个魔术
no gifts of gabs.Just one trick.
老兄 我没必要向你证明什么
Dude, I do not have to prove myself to you.
我觉得有必要
I mean, you kind of do.
让我看看天眼为什么选你
Show me why The Eye picked you.
知道吗？
You know what?
证明给我看你不需要保姆
Prove to me that you don't need a babysitter.
噢 怎么现在不演了？
Oh, what, now you stop performing?
因为你的那些废柴朋友不在你就没劲儿显摆了？
You're done showing off 'cause your misfit friends aren't here?
- 他们是我的家人 - 嗯哼
- They're my family. - Mm-hmm.
不许你说他们我不需要取悦他们
Don't you dare.I don't have to impress them.
行 算了
All right, fine. Forget it.
我只是想看看你不为了博取廉价掌声时
I just wanted to see what you were capable of.
到底有多大能耐
when you weren't trying to win cheap applause,
但我猜答案是屁能耐没有
but I guess the answer is nothing.
好吧 想看魔术是吧？
All right.You wanna see a magic trick?
看 阿特拉斯 你的问题在于
See, the problem with you, Atlas,
你总是把事情搞复杂了 老兄
is that you just like to overcomplicate things, man.
找到一颗钻石比你想像的容易多了
It is a lot easier to find a diamond than you think.
- 噢 - 让它…
- Ooh. - And to make it…
消失也一样
disappear.
- 漂亮 - 摸摸你口袋
- Nice. - Check your pocket.
- 真的？ - 是啊
Really? - Yeah.
嗯哼
Hmm.
噢 不赖 “卡牌转移到不可能的位置”
Ooh, not bad.Card to impossible location.
但别在棋盘上玩跳棋
But don't play checkers on a chessboard.
因为我已经领先你五步了
because I'm already five steps ahead of you.
摸摸你口袋
Check your pocket.
嘿
Hey.
- 那些可是无价古董 - 是啊
- Those are priceless antiques. - Yeah.
这个房间是旧文物
This room is where old relics.
最后的安息之地
go to their final resting place.
是 你大概… 大概是对的 萨迪厄斯
Yep. You are, uh… You're probably right, Thaddeus.
但在那之前 它们得有最后一次闪光的机会
But, uh, not before they have one last shot at glory.
- 这是干嘛呢？ - 挺不错
- What's going on here? - Pretty good,
但你应该试着慢一点
but you should try to do things a little more slow.
真的？
Really?
让你的观众享受真正的魔术
Let your audience enjoy the real magic.
- 好吧
Okay,
- 不赖 不赖 - 哇
- not bad. Not bad. - Wow.
干得好 博斯科
Nice one, Bosco.
我扑克一直玩得不好
I've never been great at poker,
但方片（钻石）能赢红桃吗？
but is a diamond trumped by a heart?
噢 在这儿呢 呼
Ooh. There it is.Whoo.
障眼法不错 但别忘了
Nice misdirection, but, let's not forget.
- 这到底是关于什么的 - 我还没完呢
- what this is really about. - I wasn't done.
给他看看 查理 - 把宝石变没
Show 'em, Charlie. - Making a jewel disappear.
- 来看看这个 - 好的
Let's see this one. - All right.
盯着宝物别眨眼
Keep your eye on the prize.
转啊转 转啊转 停在哪儿 谁知道
Round and round they go, where they stop, nobody knows.
没了 噢
Good as gone.Ooh.
黑背景魔术 桌子有机关 我进来就看见了
Black art, table's rigged, saw it when I came in.
- 该彻底消失了 - 噢 耶
- Time for a clean escape. - Oh, yeah.
他去哪了？我知道他在干嘛
Where is he going?I know what he's doing.
玩偶盒？这也是魔术？
Jack in the box? That's a trick?
哈 老掉牙了
Ah, it's old stuff.
早知道这么容易就把他弄走
If I had known he was that easy to get rid of.
- 没那么容易 - 是啊 杰克
- Not that easy. - Yeah, Jack.
噢 行了 暖场结束
Ohh! Okay, enough of the warm-up act,
主角该登场了
time for the headliner.
我要你想一张牌
I want you to think of one of these cards,
但别想那张你以为我想让你想的牌
but don't think of the one you think I want you to think of.
想好了吗？ 好了
Got one? Yeah, I got one.
你的牌是？红桃 4
What was your card? Four of hearts.
- 哈哈
- Ha-ha.
漂亮 教授 佩服 佩服
Nice one, professor.I'm impressed. I'm impressed.
嘿 嘿 嘿 那威士忌比你岁数还大
Hey. Hey. Hey.That whiskey is older than you.
抱歉 老板 抱歉
Sorry, boss. So sorry.
听着 各位 我不撒谎
Look, you guys, I'm not gonna lie.
这真的很酷
This has been really cool.
- 真的真的酷 - 给他们瞧瞧
- Really, really cool. - Go show 'em.
但是 我想让它更酷一点
But, uh, I think I just want to make it a little cooler.
- 来吧 耶 - 嘿
- Come on now, yeah!-Hey.
她来了 - 耶 中国雪暴
There she goes. - Yes! Snow storm in China.
成了 真美
There we are. Beautiful.
我冬天总穿白色 各位
I always wear white in winter, guys.
在法国这地方雪很少见
Snow is rare in this part of France,
但是 真冰那是不可能的
but, ice, that is just impossible.
经典 漂亮
Classic. Nice.
你怎么把消失变得这么好看？
How do you do a vanish so good?
- 噢 魔术师从不泄密 - 嗯？
- Oh, a magician never tells. - Hmm?
- 噢 嗯 - 将军
- Ooh. Hmm. - Check.
死局？
Mate?
靠
Shit.
面对现实吧 博斯科
Face it, Bosco.
智慧和技巧永远胜过年轻气盛
Wisdom and skill overcome youth and arrogance every time.
谢谢
Thank you.
永远别自以为是屋里最聪明的人 证明它
Never assume you're the smartest guy in the room. Prove it.
得了吧 老兄 你什么都没证明
Give me a break, man.You didn't prove anything.
嘿 我能提醒各位吗？
Hey, can I just remind everyone.
我们还没搞清楚
we still haven't figured out.
我们为什么会在这堆二战老古董里？
why we're even in this World War II relic?
等等
Wait!
贾斯帕·马斯基林
Jasper Maskelyne,
那个… 击败了纳粹的魔术师
the… the magician who vanquished the Nazis.
他造了假城市 假坦克
He built fake cities, fake tanks.
我是说… 我在想…
I mean… I wonder…
- 哇哦 - 噢
- Whoa. - Oh.
噢 哇
Oh, wow.
天啊 我对了？
Oh, my God, I was right?
嘿 魔术入门第一课 老兄 当魔术成功时
Hey, Magic 101, man, never act surprised.
永远别表现得像很惊讶
when the trick actually works.
噢 抱歉
Oh, sorry.
- 噢 天啊 - 这些都是什么？
- Oh, my goodness. - What is all that?
纳粹战犯百科全书
Encyclopedia of Nazi war criminals.
呃 显然包括了维罗妮卡的父亲
Uh, which apparently includes Veronika's dad.
二战后 幸存的纳粹分子逃往世界各地
After World War II, surviving Nazis fled around the world.
我不是会计 但看起来皮特·范德伯格
I'm not an accountant, but looks like Peter Vanderberg.
是靠帮他们洗黑钱发家的
got rich cleaning their dirty money.
是啊 显然维罗妮卡接手了
Yeah, and apparently Veronika took over.
利用他的犯罪网络继续作恶
right where he left off using his criminal network.
但… 但我不明白
But… But I don't understand.
天眼让我们拿这个干嘛？
What does The Eye want us to do with this?
嗯 如果我没猜错的话
Well, if I'm not mistaken,
天眼想让我们揭开范德伯格家族的面具
The Eye wants us to unmask the Vanderbergs,
用一个魔术
bring down two generations of criminals.
摧毁这个两代犯罪家族
with a single sleight of hand.
我在网上读到过
I've read some interesting rumors.
关于范德伯格的一些有趣传闻
about the Vanderbergs online.
据说 15 年前 维罗妮卡的母亲自杀了
Looks like 15 years ago, Veronika's mom killed herself,
一周后 他们管家的车刹车失灵
and a week later, their housekeeper's brakes failed.
车毁人亡 管家和她儿子都死了
Her car crashed, she and her son died.
有人怀疑是谋杀
There was some suspicion of foul play,
但一直没证据
but nothing was ever proven.
- 嗯哼
Hmm.
哇哦 该死
Whoa. Oh, shit.
警察
Police!
等等 等等
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
听好了 分头行动
Listen closely. Split up.
- 找路出去 快 快 - 好 快走
- Find a way out. Go. Go. - Okay. Come on, let's go.
他说得对 大家散开
He's right.Everybody split up.
好了 走
Okay, let's go.
我们进来了 正在寻找钻石
并不复杂 只有地滚球那么大
开始搜 别光站着
两人一组 用无线电联络
一定要找到
这边 这边
This way, this way!
站住
Stop!
- 转过去 - 转过去
- Turn around. - Turn around.
听他的 博斯科 转过去
You heard him, Bosco.Turn around.
他们来了
Here they come!
在这呢 蠢猪
再见 朋友
Adios, mon ami.
该死
抱歉
Sorry!
别跑
你好 先生 你好
Bonjour, monsieur. Bonjour.
你知道 通常 我喜欢给新客人
You know, normally, I like to give.
好好导览一番
a proper tour to new guests.
我想你已经发现了
I suspect you've discovered.
这所房子藏着许多秘密
that this house holds many secrets.
萨迪厄斯
Thaddeus!
想看个魔术吗？
Would you like to see a magic trick?
搞什么…
不如我让自己…
How about if I make myself…
消失？
disappear?
别动
Don't move!
别开枪
萨迪厄斯
Thaddeus!
搞什么…？
给我搜
他跑不远
萨迪厄斯
Thaddeus!
别动
双手抱头
快 这边
Hurry! This way!
萨迪厄斯？
Thaddeus?
噢 谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
嘿 离开这儿最快的路是哪条？
Hey, which is the fastest way out of here?
- 绕过这个弯… - 好
- Around this bend… - Yeah.
有条密道
there's a passageway.
沿着小溪穿过树林
Just follow the creek through the forest.
- 哇 - 噢
- Whoa. - Oh!
噢 不 不不不 不不不 不不不
Oh, no. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no.
不会吧？来 萨迪厄斯 站起来
This can't be happening.Come on, Thaddeus, stand up.
我们要走了
We're gonna go now.
我们得带你去治疗
We need to get you help.
求你了 站起来
Please, stand up.
你必须阻止维罗妮卡·范德伯格
You have to stop Veronika Vanderberg.
不 没有你我们做不到 萨迪厄斯
No, we can't do it without you, Thaddeus.
你们不需要我
You don't need me.
但你们需要彼此
But you do need each other.
永远别忘了这点
Never forget that.
我来的时候就知道这会是…
I knew when I came here, this was…
我最后的魔术
probably my final trick.
别让我白死
Now, don't let me die in vain.
还有事要做
There's work to be done.
走 快走 走 求你们
Go. Go now, go. Please.
趁还…
Before it's…
来得及
too late.
走吧 我们得走了
Let's go. We gotta go.
阿特拉斯
Atlas!
警察抓了琼
The police took June into custody.
那杰克和梅里特呢？
Well, what about Jack and Merritt?
- 也被抓了 - 好吧 我们去劫狱
- Them, too. - Okay, so we break them out.
等等 等等 先讨论一下
Whoa, uh-uh. Let's just talk about this for a second.
讨论什么？
Talk about what?
听我说 我们得放聪明点
Listen to me.We need to be smart.
不 我得把朋友救出来
No. We gotta get my friend out of jail.
- 博斯科… - 听着 当你调查
- Bosco… - Look, when you were researching.
我们的背景时 你知道什么没查出来吗？
all that stuff about us, you know what didn't come up?
查理和琼是我唯一的朋友
Charlie and June are my only friends.
知道我为什么喜欢他们吗？
You know what I really love about them?
因为他们不会让我觉得自己是个混蛋
They don't make me feel like an asshole.
- 我要去救琼 - 博斯科 等等…
- I'm getting June. - Bosco, wait…
- 听我说 嘿 - 就一秒 哥们
- Listen to me. Hey. - Just one second, dude.
听我说 你不能去
Listen to me. You can't.
为什么？告诉我
Why? Tell me.
他们在通缉你 博斯科
They're looking for you, Bosco.
他们在通缉我们所有人
They're looking for all of us.
是啊 没错 你也得进去
Yes. Yes, you're gonna get arrested, too.
没错
Yes.
- 靠 - 正是
- Shit. - Exactly.
要是还有别人
If only there was somebody else.
也疯到在没有资源没有保护的情况下
crazy enough to stage a jailbreak.
策划一场劫狱就好了
with no resources, no protection.
- 阿特拉斯 - 嗯？
- Atlas. - Yeah?
也许真有
Maybe there is.
萨迪厄斯·马库斯·布拉德利 如果你想知道
Thaddeus Marcus Bradley, in case you're interested.
刚才被你谋杀的人叫什么的话
in the name of the man you just murdered.
啊 是的
Ah, yes.
那是很不幸
That was unfortunate.
你知道吗 这事刚开始的时候
You know, when this whole thing started,
我对你和你那破钻石一点也不在乎
I didn't give a shit about you or your diamond,
但你非要把它变成私人恩怨
but you just went and made it deeply personal.
现在 我真的很期待能把你搞垮
And now, I am really looking forward to taking you down.
我父亲肯定会很喜欢你
My father would have loved you.
他非常喜欢魔术
He was quite fond of magic.
我五六岁的时候
When I was five or six,
在他少数几个只属于我的时刻里
in one of the few moments that I had him to myself,
他教了我一个魔术
he taught me a trick.
他会让一条红色丝绸手帕消失
He would make a red silk handkerchief disappear.
然后从嘴里吐出来
and then come back out of his mouth.
我爱死它了
I loved it!
那范儿拿捏得恰到好处
It had just the right amount of flair.
我练那个魔术练了好几个月
And I practiced that trick for months.
我想只要我表演得好
I thought that if I could do it just right,
我就能赢得他更多的…
I would earn more of…
关注
of him.
但这只是幻觉
But that was the illusion.
从那以后我就讨厌魔术
I've hated magic ever since.
那些浮夸 俗套的东西 更别提像你这种
The camp, the cheese, not to say anything.
玩读心术的骗子
of con artists like you with your mentalism.
我们俩都没有超能力 麦金尼先生
Neither one of us has psychic powers, Mr. McKinney.
但你也不需要 你知道我的“海洋之心”在哪儿
But you don't have to.You know where my Heart is.
而我也一样
And I don't have to,
因为你会告诉我的
because you're going to tell me.
我想你足够聪明
I think you're smart enough to know that.
知道用我们德州话说就是 我屁都不会告诉你
I ain't telling you shit, as we say in Texas.
而且 关于读心术你错了
And, you're wrong about mentalism.
人们把整个人生故事都写在了脸上
People wear their entire life story on their face.
你只需要知道怎么读
You just have to know how to read it.
拿你的来说吧
Take yours, for example.
- 可以吗？ - 请便
- May I? - With pleasure.
这下有意思了
This is gonna be fun.
好吧 你已经
Well, you've already shared,
非常痛苦详细地 分享了你缺父爱的事
in excruciating detail, your daddy issues,
但我很好奇你妈妈
but I'm curious about your mom.
她为什么要自杀？
Why did she commit suicide?
她也像你一样
Was she as desperate.
绝望地渴望你父亲的关注吗？
for your father's attention as you were?
噢…
Ooh…
她是
She was.
那是为什么呢？
And why was that?
是你父亲把关注给了别人吗？
Did your father give his attention to someone else?
你把头发撩到耳后 那就是破绽
When you tuck your hair behind your ear, that's a tell.
的确如此
He was.
所以 他是跟秘书搞上了？
So, was he banging his secretary?
不 那太俗套了
No, that's too cliche.
一定是个和你妈妈很亲近的人才会让她…
But it had to be someone close to your mom for her to…
好朋友？理发师？
A good friend? Hairdresser?
该不会是管家吧？
It wasn't the housekeeper, was it?
不 不是管家
No, not the housekeeper.
我没空跟你废话
I don't have time for this.
通常我说对了的时候人们都这么说
And that's what people usually say when I'm getting hot.
要不要把空调开大点 或者开个窗？
Should we crank up the AC, maybe open a window?
听着 如果我爸跟管家有一腿
Now, if my dad was having sex with my housekeeper.
我妈发现后自杀了
and my mom found out and committed suicide,
我大概不会去弄坏管家那辆车的刹车
I probably wouldn't cut the brakes on my housekeeper's car.
毕竟 我又不是变态
But then again, I'm not a psychopath.
你是个可悲又可怜的男人
You are a sad and pathetic man.
我明白你为什么要自杀了
I can see why you want to end it.
呃 嘿 那个 维罗妮卡…
Uh, hey, uh, Veronika…
你知道吗
You know,
逃跑也是破绽
walking away is also a tell.
局长 我在公园里抓到这个老巫婆
她喝得酩酊大醉 怎么处理？
我能把你喝趴下 蠢猪
把她关进去
蠢猪
喔啦啦
Ooh-la-la.
这间是我的？
我要海景房
先生 先生 先生
Monsieur, monsieur, monsieur.
呜 他好可爱
快走…
我们为这位囚犯负全责
范德伯格女士 无意冒犯 我不能…
不 你们不能再处理她了
局长 那个老巫婆的胳膊断了
什么？
我们必须叫救护车
她的胳膊断了 正在耷拉着 局长
哪去了？那个女孩呢？
Where is she? Where's the girl?
妈的
Shit!
找到她
她跑了
She escaped.
找到那个女孩
晚上好
Bonsoir.
这也太恶心了 就算是你
That's pretty disgusting, even for you.
我可能酒喝多了
I think I may have overdone it on the wine.
嗨 露拉
Hi, Lula.
顺便说一句 你气色不错
You look great, by the way.
好吧 第一…
Okay, one…
我以为再也见不到你了
I didn't think I'd ever see you again.
你怎么找到我们的？
How did you find us?
有人给我报信了
A little birdie told me.
想想我多惊讶
Imagine my surprise.
你们居然撇下我重组了
You guys all got back together without me.
什么？不 不是那样 你不明白
What? No, it's not like that.You don't understand.
不是吗？是吗？
It wasn't? No?
你自由了 混蛋
You're free. Dick.
救兵到了
The cavalry.
- 想我吗？ - 噢 想死你了
- Miss me? - Oh, a lot.
噢 你好啊 我是露拉…
Oh, hello there.It's me, Lula…
大牙 露拉
Teeth! Lula!
记得吗？我曾经也是四骑士
Remember?I too was once a Horseman.
是啊 我问过你 我是唯一问起你的人
Yeah, I asked about you.I was the only one.
噢 你是唯… 他是唯一问起的人？真的吗？
Oh, you were the…He was the only one. Really?
站住
该死 好吧
Shit. Okay.
我们得去汇合点 计划是这样的
We have to get to the meet-up.Okay, here's the plan.
我搞到了逃逸车 一切就绪
I have the getaway car. It's all ready to go.
只需要杰克去接线打火
I just need Jack to hotwire it.
等等 你的计划是让我去偷车？
Wait, your plan is for me to steal a car?
嗯哼
Uh-huh!
好吧 我去打火 你去找琼
Okay, I'll hotwire the car.You get June.
一定要带上她 明白吗？
Do not leave without her, all right?
- 外面汇合 - 好好好 没问题
- Meet us outside. - Yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay.
噢 注意闪烁的警灯
Oh! Uh, watch for flashing lights!
知道吗 我可以接线…
Okay. You know, I can hotwire the…
- 你可以放开我了 - 好 抱歉
- You can let go of me now. - Right. Sorry.
别动
♪ Oui-Oui（A Canadian in Paris） - Pulsallama ♪
老实点 小孩
♪ 法兰西万岁 ♪
♪ Viva la France ♪
♪ 我爱薯条和吐司 ♪
♪ I love the fries and the toast ♪
过来
Come here.
钻石在哪？
Where is the diamond?
梅里特 谢谢
Merritt, thank you.
有我保护你 小孩
Got your back, kiddo.
那谁来保护你？
But who's got yours?
闪烁的灯光
Flashing lights.
跑
Run!
看着我的眼睛
Look into my eyes,
注视并思考为何我的低语
watch and wonder why I whisper words.
削弱了你的意志 然后 睡
that weaken your will, and sleep.
看来不是对谁都管用
Not everyone's susceptible.
我说 “睡 ”
I said, "Sleep!"
别激动 拜托了
Easy does it s'il vous plait.
当当
Ta-da!
哈啰？
Hello?
杰克？
Jack?
你应该早告诉我们你是坐警车来的
You could have told us you were coming in a police car.
真是多谢了
Thank you very much.
看 我们让第五位骑士重现了
And, look, we made the Fifth Horseman reappear.
- 你好 露拉 - 嗨
- Hello, Lula. - Hi.
好了
Okay.
- 没事吧？ - 没事 我没事
- Are you okay? - Yeah. No, I'm okay. I'm okay.
- 但他们抓了梅里特 - 该死
- But they have Merritt. - Shit.
- 是啊 我跑了 他没跑掉 - 好了好了
- Yeah, I escaped, he couldn't. - Yeah, yeah.
大家都挺激动的
Very emotional time for everybody here.
显然发生了很多事
Clearly a lot going on.
我也尽量不往心里去
And I'm really trying not to take any of this personally.
但能不能告诉我
But, please, can you tell me,
天眼直接联系你了？
did The Eye contact you directly?
是啊
Yeah.
- 你也是？ - 对
- You, too? - Yes.
- 你怎么不早给我打电话？ - 抱歉
- Why didn't you call me sooner? - I'm so sorry.
- 我得找保姆啊 - 得了吧
- I had to find a babysitter. - Come on!
一切发生得太快了
Everything happened like that.
等等 抱歉 你们认识？
Wait, sorry.You two know each other?
- 认识 - 当然认识…
- Yeah. - Yeah, we know…
你觉得这世上
How many female magicians do you think.
有多少女魔术师？
there are in the world?
我们这屋里居然能有三个
The fact there are three of us in the room right now.
太惊人了 惊人
Shocking. Shocking.
- 简直不可思议 - 确实
- It's, like, mind blown. - That's true.
宇宙居然没因此坍缩 真让我惊讶
I'm surprised the universe isn't folding in on itself.
- 就是说啊 - 阿布扎比
- Exactly. - Abu Dhabi!
- 他一直这样吗？ - 嗯哼
- Does he just do that? - Mm-hmm.
抱歉 我… 我是你的超级粉丝
Sorry, I just… I'm a big fan of yours, by the way.
我刚才在查维罗妮卡下一步去哪儿
I was trying to figure out where Veronika was gonna be next.
显然 范德伯格集团有一支赛车队
And, apparently, Vanderberg Global has a motorsports team.
这周末要在阿布扎比发布新车
They're introducing a new car this weekend in Abu Dhabi.
所以我们可以把梅里特救回来 顺便揭露她
So we can get Merritt back and expose her.
对 没错
Yeah. Yeah.
不不不 我不揭露她
No, no, no.I am not exposing her.
我不揭露任何人 好吗？
I am not exposing anyone, okay?
我不管天眼想干嘛 不干了
I don't care what The Eye wants. No.
我们用这个换梅里特 然后就收手
We are swapping this for Merritt, and then we are done.
我们救朋友 不救世界
We're saving our friend, we're not saving the world.
- 然后呢？ - 什么？
- And then what? - What?
我们就回去过日子让她逍遥法外？
We just go back to our lives and let her walk away?
俄罗斯那次之后你说过 “魔术师是艺人
After Russia, you said, "Magicians are entertainers,
- “不是超级英雄” - 天啊 又来了
- "not superheroes."-Oh, my God. Here we go.
我现在觉得你是对的
And I'm starting to think that you were right.
她不像她父亲那样只洗钱
She doesn't just launder money like her father.
你看到萨迪厄斯的下场了
You saw what happened to Thaddeus.
显然 我有点跟不上节奏了 对吧？
Obviously, I'm playing a bit of catch-up here, right?
我没有掌握全部信息
I don't have all of the information,
但这不妨碍我
but I don't think that that should stop me.
发表一下对下一步行动的看法
from having an opinion about what we do next.
- 确实妨碍 - 没错
- Of course it should. - Exactly.
不妨碍 阿特拉斯
No, it shouldn't, Atlas.
我觉得我们应该揭露凡妮莎
And I think we should expose Vanessa.
- 维罗妮卡 - 维罗妮卡
- Veronika. - Veronika.
揭露她谋杀和…
For murder and…
- 另一件事是什么？ - 洗钱
- What is the other thing? - Money laundering.
和洗钱
And for money laundering.
谋杀和洗钱
For murder and for money laundering.
- 对 没错 - 我们应该把她绑起来…
- Yeah. Yeah. - We should tie her up…
不 不行 太危险了
No, no! It is too dangerous!
- 阿特拉斯说得对 - 什么？
- And Atlas is right. - What?
我们再也不牺牲自己了
We are done sacrificing ourselves.
- 是啊 - 抱歉 不值得
- Yeah. - I'm sorry. It's not worth it.
真是放屁
That's bullshit!
啥？你错了
What?You're wrong.
- 我错了？ - 抱歉
- Am I? - Sorry.
不 别道歉 说出来
No. Don't be sorry. Say it.
你是错了 你错了 只是…
You are.You're wrong. It's just…
在发现四骑士之前
Before I discovered the Horsemen,
我对什么都不在乎
I didn't give a shit about anything.
我… 我的家人抛弃了我
I… My family gave me up.
我憎恨整个世界
I hated the whole world.
然后 我看到了你们的视频
And then, I saw a video of you guys,
你们试图让这个世界
and you were trying to make the world.
变得不那么腐败 不那么糟糕
less corrupt, less terrible.
这让我重新燃起了希望
And that made me give a shit.
魔术怎么玩？
So what's the trick?
我保证会成功的
I promise this is gonna work.
但这足以转移注意力吗？
But is that enough misdirection?
只要她人在现场
As long as she's here and not there.
我们就能搞定
We can take care of that.
就算你们只晚了五分钟…
If you're even just five minutes late…
- 五分钟？我看一分钟都不行 - 迟到一分钟
- Five? I'd say one. - One minute late.
我们怎么知道会有足够多的人到场？
How do we know enough people are gonna show up?
伙计们 这消息已经传疯了
You guys, it's already viral.
我保证会人山人海
I guarantee there'll be a crowd.
这太疯狂了 变数太多了
This is nuts.There's too many variables.
嘿 我们会一直跟你们保持联系
Hey, we'll be in constant contact with you.
- 如果出了差错… - 嘿 嘿 嘿
- if something goes awry… - Hey, hey, hey.
这事儿没有任何犯错的馀地 明白吗？零容错
There's, like, no margin for error here, man. Okay? Zero.
我们必须做到完美无缺
We're going to have to be absolutely flawless.
要想在这短得离谱的时间内
if we're gonna pull something this risky off.
搞定这么多环节
with this many moving parts.
完成这么高风险的任务 好吗？
in this ridiculously short amount of time, okay?
- 是的 - 对
- Yes. - Yeah.
不过 至少代表我自己说一句
But speaking for myself, at least,
我觉得我们七个人联手胜算比谁都大
I think the seven of us have a better chance than most.
噢
Oh.
瞧瞧
Would you look at this?
伟大的博斯科·勒罗伊什么时候变温柔了？
When did the great Bosco Leroy go soft?
好了 各位 这票干还是不干？
Okay, guys, are we doing this or what?
这可是千万分之一的机率
It is a ten million to one shot.
我就喜欢这种机率
Those are my kind of odds.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
吉时已到
the time has come.
今晚 仅此一晚
Tonight, for one night only.
凑近点 再近点
Come in close.Closer.
阿联酋 - 阿布扎比
因为你自以为看清的越多…
'Cause the more you think you see…
就越容易被蒙骗过去
The easier it will be to fool you.
倒计时开始
The countdown begins.
只需两小时
In only two hours,
四骑士将再次同台
the Four Horsemen will be on stage together.
这是十年来的第一次
for the first time in ten years.
J·丹尼尔·阿特拉斯
J. Daniel Atlas.
亨利·里维斯
Henley Reeves.
杰克·怀尔德
Jack Wilder.
还有露拉·梅
And Lula May.
女士们先生们 四骑士
Ladies and gentlemen, the Four Horsemen.
没错 四骑士回归仅此一晚
That's right, the Horsemen are back for one night only.
上周 我们偷走了海洋之心
Now, last week, we stole the Heart Diamond,
今晚 两小时后
and tonight, in two hours' time,
我们要把它物归原主
we're going to return it to its rightful owner,
还给你们所有人
all of you.
你觉得这引起她注意了吗？
Do you think that got her attention?
这要不行 我也没辙了
If that didn't, I don't know what will.
听着 现在你知道
All right, listen, now that you know.
事情会有多糟糕了
how bad things can actually get,
能不能就这一次稳一点？
can you please just try playing it safe this one time?
- 不能 - 行吧
- No. - Okay.
噢
Oh.
她来了 真准时
Here she is. Right on time.
演出好看吗？
You enjoying the show?
呃 对我来说有点俗气
Eh, it's a little tacky for my taste.
我想你把场地选在这是因为离我很近吧
I assume you chose your venue for its proximity to my own.
好吧 告诉你个好消息
Well, good news for you.
我已经把你列入宾客名单了
I've placed you on our guest list.
带上我的海洋之心 我们来做个交换
Bring me my Heart.We'll make an exchange.
用麦金尼先生换钻石
Mr. McKinney for the diamond.
- 嗯哼 - 在外面 灯光下
Mm-hmm. - Outside, under the lights,
别耍任何魔术花招
and not the first hint of magic.
要是帽子里蹦出个兔子
One rabbit comes out of a hat,
或者袖子里滑出张牌
one ace slides out of a sleeve,
你的朋友就会“嘭”的一声 没命了
and your friend goes poof.
我只是想用点你能听懂的术语
Just trying to use parlance you'd understand.
♪ Abracadabra - Lady Gaga ♪
♪ 阿布拉卡达布拉… ♪
♪ Abracadabra, amor-oo-na-na ♪
♪ Abracadabra Morta-oo-ga-ga ♪
♪ 阿布拉卡达布拉… ♪
♪ Abracadabra, abra-oo-na-na ♪
♪ 她说着 ♪
♪ In her tongue she said ♪
♪ “今晚不是死就是爱” ♪
♪ "Death or love tonight" ♪
♪ 阿布拉卡达布拉 阿布拉卡达布拉 ♪
♪ Abracadabra, abracadabra ♪
♪ 阿布拉卡达布拉 阿布拉卡达布拉… ♪
♪ Abracadabra Abracadabra… ♪
欢迎来到亚斯岛 W 酒店
Welcome to the W Yas Island.
中东的奥兰多
The Orlando of the Middle East.
哈
Ha.
最后
Now, finally,
感谢亚斯岛举办了一场
thank you to Yas Island for hosting an event.
配得上赛车界最快车队的活动
worthy of the fastest team in motorsport.
这条赛道是顶级的
This track is elite,
但它很快就会让我们的对手
but it will soon provide our competitors.
看到赛车中最常见的景象
with the most common view in racing,
那就是我们的车尾灯
the rear wings of our cars.
谢谢
Thank you.
天啊 那是维罗妮卡？
Holy shit. That's Veronika?
她气场很强啊
She has a very commanding presence.
我们的魔术朋友到了
Our magical friends have arrived.
去招呼他们一下吧
Why don't you go and greet them?
非常感谢光临 希望你们喜欢比赛
Thank you so much for coming.I hope you enjoy the race.
好吧 阿特拉斯说要制造混乱
Okay, Atlas said to create a distraction.
我们怎么搞？
How are we gonna pull this off?
到处都是保安
There is security everywhere.
好了 别慌 交给我
Okay, you guys, calm down.I got this.
嗨 你好
Hello. Hi.
呃 大卫 酷 我是媒体公关部的
Uh, David. Cool.I'm from media relations.
我就是来确认一下
I was just checking in.
你们能不能换个机位？
Do you think you guys could do a different camera placement?
好的 谢了 继续
Okay, thanks. Continue.
那是谁？
Who is that?
该你了
Your turn.
动手吧
Let's do this.
务必确认
Make sure you confirm.
钻石的真伪
the authenticity of the diamond.
这帮人诡计多端
These people are very tricky.
很高兴你能来
I'm so glad you came.
我们要不言归于好？
What do you say we bury the hatchet?
- 往彼此脖子上砍那种？ - 哈 他真幽默
- In each other's necks? - Ha! He's funny.
我们各自拥有对方想要的东西
We each possess something beneficial to the other.
做生意的完美理由
Perfect reason to do business.
只有一点警告
Only, there's one caveat.
我热切希望我们的交集到此为止
I fervently hope our mutual dealings are at a close.
- 她真淡定 - 别说话
- She's so poised. - Not now.
- 我恨她… 呃 - 露拉 嘘
- I hate her… Ugh. - Lula. Shh.
- 怎么样？ - 哥们 有事吗？
- How's it going? - Bro, can I help you?
对 我们要拍这辆车
Yeah, we're here to shoot the car.
- 证件？ - 噢 对 当然
- ID? - Oh, right. Of course.
必须的 给
Obviously. There you are.
- 你的呢？ - 呃 那个
- And you? - Uh, yeah,
在我夹克里
it's in my jacket somewhere.
找到了
There it is.
我们是《方格旗》摄制组的 拍纪录片的
We're with Checkered Flags, the doc series.
下一季拍范德伯格车队
Next season's on Vanderberg Motorsports.
他们居然没通知你们？
They seriously didn't give you guys a heads-up?
典型作风
Typical.
我们只需要拍点插入镜头 可能还要点空镜
We're just gonna get some inserts, maybe some B-roll.
还有围观这辆豪车的人群
and some party people gawking at this beauty.
- 好了 只要你… - 喂 别碰车
- All right, whenever you're… - Oi, don't touch the car.
- 我们得拍内饰 - 对
- We got to shoot the interior. - Yeah.
我甚至可以让你在片子里露个脸
I can actually get you a cameo in this thing.
- 省省吧 我有命令在身 - 是啊 我们也有
- Save it. I've got my orders. - Yeah, and so do we.
晚上好 范德伯格女士
Good evening, Ms. Vanderberg.
对 我们正要拍您要的素材
Yeah. We're trying to get that footage you asked for,
但遇到了一点小麻烦
but we ran into a little bit of a problem.
- 你要有麻烦了 - 她要跟你说话
- You're gonna be in trouble. - She wants to talk to you.
不妙啊 老兄 啧啧 不妙
That's not good, my guy.Mm-mm. Not good.
喂？
Hello.
听着 我父亲常说
Listen, my father always said.
没人会买没见过的钻石
no one buys a diamond sight unseen.
而此时此刻 我的车就是那颗钻石
And at this very moment, my car is the diamond.
所以 要么让他们干活
So, you can either let them do their job,
要么你自己另谋高就
or you can find yourself a new one.
抱歉耽误了 女士
Sorry for the hold-up, ma'am.
- 没事了 - 你最棒了
- You're good. - You're the best.
麻烦稍微退后一点？
If you could just back up for me really quick?
为了光线 谢了兄弟
Just for the light. Thanks, man.
好了 开始吧？
Well, shall we get on with it?
请
Please.
噢 当然 你带了打手 原谅我的冒犯
Oh. Of course, you have a goon. Forgive me.
啊 拜托 你不信我们？
Ah, come on, you don't trust us?
经历了这么多事？
After all we've been through?
有什么问题吗？
Is there a problem?
不确定的话再仔细查查
Double check if you're not certain.
- 是海洋之心 - 当然是
- It's the Heart. - Yes, of course it is.
现在 拜托 能把朋友还给我们了吗？
Now, please, can you get our friend?
过来
Come on.
来了 好的
There he is. Okay.
哎 嘿
Ah! Hey.
- 呼 - 没事吧？
- Whew. - You okay?
既然知道我值五亿美元了
Well, now that I know I'm worth half a billion dollars.
我觉得我们还是亏了 不过见到你真好
I still think we got ripped off, but it's good to see you.
板上钉钉 这就交货
Signed, sealed, delivered.
看 我是个守信用的女人
See, I'm a woman of my word.
想留下来也行 享受派对
Stick around if you want, enjoy the party.
嘿 嘿
Hey! Hey!
搞什么鬼？
What in God's name?
- 妈的 - 闪开
- Shit! - Step aside!
快点 这玩意怎么开啊？
Come on, how do you make this thing go?
你这么吼我我没法集中精神
I can't concentrate with you yelling at me!
别让他跑了
Don't let him get away!
借过
Excuse me!
报警
Call the police!
演出好看吗？
You enjoying the show?
你是打算傻站着看还是去把我的车追回来？
You just gonna stand there gawking or get my car back?
你搞的鬼
You did this.
好了 走起
Okay, here we go.
好了 阿特拉斯 你想要混乱
Okay, Atlas, you wanted a distraction,
给你混乱
you got a distraction.
天 这玩意甩尾太厉害了
Man, this thing is tail happy.
噢 天 什么鬼？
Oh, man, what the hell?
我们掉进活板门里了
We fell through a trapdoor or something.
大家都还好吗？
Is everybody okay?
- 这是哪儿？ - 不好
- Where are we? - No.
今天早上醒来时 除了我的钻石
When I woke up this morning, there was only one thing.
我唯一想要的就是
I wanted more than my diamond.
把四骑士关起来
My Horsemen under lock and key.
现在我两者兼得
And now that I have both,
我得承认 我都要被宠坏了
I must admit, I'm feeling a little bit spoiled.
在你们准备那点小把戏的时候
While you were prepping your little performance,
我也策划了一个我自己的魔术
I curated a trick of my own.
困住五位骑士 无处可逃
Five Horsemen trapped, no escape.
你们五个或许是国家宝藏
You five may be national treasures,
但我们这儿也有宝藏
but we have those here, too.
只是很难找
Only they're hard to find,
因为它们被埋在沙子里
because they're buried in sand.
对世人来说 你们死于
To the world, it will appear you died.
一次失败的逃生表演
in a failed escape act.
现在 让我们见识下魔术吧
Now, let's see some magic.
去他妈的魔术 快叫增援
Fuck magic!Somebody call for backup!
- 杰克 打给琼 - 谁有信号？
Jack, call June. - Anyone have service?
天 她肯定屏蔽了手机信号
God, she must have scrambled the cell signal.
她算无遗策啊
She thought of everything!
露拉 你到底哪头的？
Lula, whose side are you on?
我当然是我们这头的 但她确实算无遗策
I'm on our side, obviously, but she also thought of everything.
这两点又不冲突
Both things can be true at one time.
沙子越来越高了 沙子越来越多了
The sand is getting higher.The sand is getting bigger.
沙子多了 体积也大了
There's more sand and it's getting larger.
亨利 亨利 逃生第一原则
Henley, Henley, uh, first principle of escape.
呃 生存时间还有多久？对
Uh, how long is it survivable? Right.
对 好 根据流速判断
Right. Great. Judging from the rate of the flow,
箱子的体积…
the volume of the box…
- 呃 完了 我们死定了 - 噢 太棒了
- Uh, yeah, we're screwed. - Oh, amazing.
好吧 那逃生第二原则呢？
Okay, how about the second principle of escape then?
那是关于箱子本身的
Okay, so that's the box itself.
有缺陷吗？有弱点吗？
Is there a flaw?Is there a weakness?
有后门吗？
Is there a back door?
大家都检查一下
Everybody just needs to check!
这边封死了
This side's sealed.
该死 不 封死了 封死了 封死了
Shit. No, it's sealed, sealed, sealed.
到处都封死了
Everything's sealed.
有没有第三原则？
Any chance there's a third principle?
我有你要的东西
I have what you're after.
完美
Perfect.
我在“海洋之心”的归处等你
I will meet you where the Heart resides.
我迫不及待了
I can hardly wait.
直奔金库
Straight to the vault.
不不不不 耶
No, no, no, no! Yes!
救我 瑞奇·鲍比 救我
Help me, Ricky Bobby! Help me!
真的要这样吗？
Is this really gonna happen right now?
我们就这样死在这个箱子里？真的？
We're just gonna die here in this box? Really?
真讽刺 一周前 我还想死呢
It's funny. A week ago, I wanted to die,
然后… 我就找回了活下去的理由
and then… then I get my reason to live back,
结果现在 我真的要死了
and now, we're actually gonna die.
这哪里好笑了？
How is that funny?
那个 我是说 在我脑子里挺好笑的
Well, I mean, it was funnier in my head.
就是… 你知道 那种诡异的好笑
It's… You know, it's peculiar funny.
不 别说了 不
No. Uh-uh. No.
我们没辙了
We're out of options.
天啊 我不该那么刻薄
God, I never should have been that horrible.
吐槽你的网站 服装还有标志
about your website and your costumes and the logo.
- 好吧 - 其实并不尴尬
- Okay. - It's not embarrassing.
“Wilder”里的“I”是根小魔杖
that the "I" in "Wilder"is a little magic wand.
- 我知道了 那… - 不尴尬
- I got it. That's… - It's not.
- 谢谢 - 挺可爱的 挺迷人的
- Thank you. - It's cute and it's charming.
- 够了 - 还有我… 我想你们了
- That's enough. - And I… I missed you.
听着 我知道我平时不表现出来 但是…
Listen, I know I don't always show it, but, um…
你们对我真的很重要
I really do think the world of all of you.
我不敢相信我们要被活埋了
I cannot believe we're getting buried alive.
- 这简直像西部片 - 等等 等等 活埋
- I mean, it's like a Western. - Wait, wait. Buried alive.
那是… 魔术的老传统了
That's, like, an old magic tradition.
抱歉 谁表演过来着？
Sorry, who do we know who did that?
比尔·舍克差点因此丧命 记得吗？
Bill Shirk nearly died doing that. Remember?
他进了有机玻璃棺材然后被沙子埋了
He got into a Plexiglas coffin and had it covered in sand.
但玻璃不是碎了吗？
But didn't the Plexiglas break?
- 沙子湿了 - 沙子湿了
- The sand got wet. - The sand got wet.
我想起来了 前一天晚上下雨了
I remember now.It rained the night before.
对 湿沙子比干沙子重 压碎了玻璃
Okay, wet sand is heavier than dry. It broke the glass.
等等 等等 等等 如果我们弄断那根管子
Wait, wait, wait, wait.If we broke that pipe,
就能弄湿沙子
then it would wet the sand,
然后它就会… 压垮箱子 对吧？
and then it'll…it'll break the box, right?
如果我能… 如果我能缠住它
If I could… If I could wrap something around it,
我就能借力把它弄断
I might be able to get some leverage.
好的
Okay.
梅里特 把皮带给我
Merritt, give me your belt.
好的 好的 给你 给你
Okay.Okay, you got it. You got it.
- 嗯 好了 好了 - 加油
- Yep, okay, okay. - Come on.
- 很好 很好 很好 - 你行的
Good, good, good. - You got this.
- 你行的 - 加油 加油
- You got this. - Come on. Come on.
- 耶 耶 - 耶
- Yes! Yes!-Yes!
帮我 帮我 把我往下拉
Help me! Help me! Pull me down!
- 好 好 来 来 来 - 这是金属做的
- Okay, okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah. - It's made up of metal.
漂亮 漂亮 漂亮 好了
Nice, nice, nice, okay.
靠边停车 你已经被包围了
Pull over.You have been surrounded.
我倒是想停车
I'd love to pull over,
但我终于找到点手感了
but I'm finally getting the hang of this.
你们俩跟着他
我是世界上最棒的车手
I'm the greatest driver in the world!
马上进入市场
去另一边截住他
不不不不
No, no, no, no.
小心
Watch out!
该死
Damn it!
熄火 下车
Turn off the engine and exit the vehicle.
你被包围了
We've got you surrounded.
举起手来 不许动
Put your hands up and don't move!
抱歉 我是不是忘了打转向灯？
I'm sorry. Did I forget to use my blinker?
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
谢谢各位 干得漂亮
Thank you, gentlemen.Excellent work.
我们对博斯科·勒罗伊发出了红色通缉令
We've had a red notice for one Bosco Leroy.
- 谢谢 - 没问题
- Thank you. - No problem.
完了 阿特拉斯会杀了我的
Yep, Atlas is gonna kill me.
- 水进得太快了 - 玻璃打不破
- Water's coming in too fast. - And the glass won't break.
- 就为了一颗钻石 - 我们现在能用上它
- All this for a diamond. - We could use that now.
只有钻石才能切割玻璃
Nothing cuts glass like a diamond.
等等 等等 等等 等等 亨利 亨利
Wait, whoa, whoa.Wait, Henley. Henley.
对 我能闭气八分钟
Yes! I can hold my breath for eight minutes.
如果有人能逃出去 那就是我们
If anyone can get us out of this, we can.
我们要穿越沙漠了 女士
We're crossing into the desert, ma'am.
沙尘暴越来越大了
The dust storm is getting worse.
他在这干什么？
What's he doing here?
范德伯格女士的钻石被你和你的朋友偷了？
Ms. Vanderberg's diamond that you and your friends stole?
丢东西了吗？
Lost something?
真好玩
That was fun.
- 成功了 - 成功了
- It's working! - It's working.
大家帮忙
Everybody help!
- 帮忙 - 搞起 来
- Everybody help!-Let's do it! Come on!
快
Come on.
亨利 干得好
Henley, way to go!
- 天啊 - 干得漂亮
- Oh, my God!-Nice job!
好了 我们还得赶场演出
All right, we got a show to catch.
希望还不算太晚
I hope we're not too late.
- 没事吧？ - 没事
- You all right? - Yeah.
身份验证通过
Identity verified.
你来了
You made it.
你有我想要的东西吗？
Do you have what I want?
如果你有我想要的话
If you have what I want.
证据呢？
Where's the evidence?
就在这儿
Right here.
我就是证据
I'm the evidence.
查理 我… 我不…
Charlie, I… I don't…
你死了
You're dead.
现在你看到我了
Now you see me.
真有意思 人们为了让…
It's quite fascinating the things people do.
某样东西或某个人
to make something or someone…
消失
disappear.
啊
Ah.
我教过你这个魔术
I taught you that trick.
就像父亲教你一样
Just like our father taught you.
而现在 15 年后 你…
And now, after 15 years, you're…
你想毁了我？
you're trying to ruin me?
不
No.
是整整 15 年
All 15 years.
我不知道你会在那辆车里
I didn't know you'd be in that car.
但你听说我在里面时一定松了口气
But you must have been relieved to hear I was.
当我们落水时
When we hit the water,
我解不开安全带
I couldn't unbuckle my seat belt.
妈妈用最后一口气救了我
Mom freed me with her dying breath.
我对你只有喜爱 查理
I had nothing but fondness for you, Charlie.
让我最后把你当弟弟对待一次
Let me finally treat you like a brother.
我就是你弟弟
I am your brother!
我们都流着父亲的血
Father's blood is in both of us,
尽管他从未承认过我
though he'd never acknowledge mine.
天知道妈妈怎么求他的
God knows Mother begged.
耻辱地把我母亲逼进了坟墓
And the shame drove my mother to her grave.
然后你就把我母亲也送进去了
Then you sent mine to hers!
好吧
Fine.
你是对的
You're right.
它该归你
It should be yours.
给
Here.
拿着
Take it.
徒手接子弹
Bullet catch.
- 这不可能 - 不 这只是魔术
- That's impossible. - No. Just magic.
啊
Ah.
嗯
Hmm.
大家好
Hello, everyone.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了 谢谢
All right, thank you.
今晚早些时候 阿特拉斯
Earlier tonight, J. Daniel Atlas.
承诺将“海洋之心”
promised to return the Heart Diamond.
物归原主
to its rightful owner.
但在那之前
But before we do that,
有些介绍要做
some introductions are in order.
首先 让我们欢迎自然之力
First, let's say hello to the fierce force of nature,
非凡的琼·鲁克莱尔
the extraordinary June Rouclere!
耶 琼
Yeah, June!
哇 大家好 谢谢
Wow. Hello, everyone. Thank you.
非常感谢 谢谢
Thank you so much. Thank you.
接下来是不屈不挠的
And give it up for the indomitable.
博斯科·勒罗伊
Bosco Leroy!
荣幸之至
The pleasure is ours.
你好啊 美女
Hello, gorgeous.
当然
要是没有
And, of course, we could not have done.
世界上最伟大的魔术师相助
any of this in the first place.
我们也做不到这一切
without the help of the world's greatest magicians.
四…
The Four…
抱歉 是五骑士
Sorry, make that Five Horsemen!
谢谢大家
Thank you, everyone.
哇 呃…
Wow. Uh…
你知道 我们娱乐过
You know, we have entertained, well,
震撼过世界各地的观众
dazzled audiences all over the world,
但我们从未参与过这样的魔术
but we have never been part of a trick like this.
你们可能会问
And you may be asking yourself,
“他们是怎么做到的？”
"How did they pull this off?"
好吧 每个魔术师都需要一个助手 维罗妮卡？
Okay, well, every magician needs an assistant. Veronika?
你们可能认为维罗妮卡
You may think Veronika here,
作为皮特·范德伯格的唯一继承人
as Peter Vanderberg's sole heir,
是这颗钻石的合法主人
is the rightful owner of this diamond.
但是 反转来了
But, here's the twist.
皮特不止一个孩子 他有两个
Peter didn't have one child.He had two.
没错
That's right.
另一个孩子死里逃生
And that other child cheated death.
到了纽约
And landed in New York City.
在那里复仇成了他一生的使命
Where vengeance became his life's work.
但他需要帮手
But he would need help.
噢 找到威士忌了 谢了
Oh. Found the scotch. Thanks.
所以他招兵买马
So he recruited.
告诉我什么时候停
when to stop, tell me when.
停
Stop.
- 是你的牌吗？ - 是
- Is that your card? - Yes.
是吧？想知道我是怎么做到的吗？
Yeah? You want to know how I did it?
引诱…
Enticed…
笼络了他能找到的
and lured some of the most.
最聪明的头脑
brilliant minds he could assemble,
为一场前所未有的魔术奠定基础
laying the groundwork for a trick unlike any other.
直到今晚
Which brings us to tonight.
为这一切的幕后主脑欢呼吧
Make some noise for the mastermind behind all of this.
我们要好的朋友
Our best friend.
- 一个幽灵… - 直到此刻
- A ghost… - Until this very moment.
查理·范德伯格
Charlie Vanderberg!
- 哇 - 呼
- Wow. - Whoo!
我知道我说过我很享受搞垮你
I know I said I'd enjoy taking you down,
但这比我预想的还要好玩
but this is more fun than I anticipated.
你还是个可悲又可怜的男人
You are still a sad and pathetic man.
而你什么都不是
And you are nothing.
噢 等等 各位 稍等
Oh, hold on, everyone. One sec.
- 永远都会是 - 那是什么？
- And you never will be. - What's that?
我不明白你们是怎么做到的
I don't understand how you pulled this off.
你不明白？
You don't understand?
维罗妮卡似乎不明白
Veronika doesn't seem to understand.
她是怎么落到这步田地的
how she found herself in this position.
好吧 让我们给她解释一下
Well, let's explain it to her.
你看 最高明的魔术利用的就是思维定势
You see, the finest magic preys on assumptions.
比如以为接你的那辆车
That the car waiting for you.
就是送你来的那辆
was the same one that dropped you off.
走吧
Let's go.
以为大自然的杰作就真的只是自然现象
That an act of Mother Nature is nothing but.
以为沙漠里的金库
And that a vault in the desert.
就不可能是障眼法
isn't just smoke and mirrors.
以为枪里装的不是空包弹
That a gun isn't filled with blanks.
以为电梯
And that an elevator.
就真的只是在往下降
is just simply descending into earth.
想骗过欺诈大师
If you want to trick the master of deception,
你就得操纵她的现实
you have to manipulate her reality.
作为最后一个魔术
And for our last trick,
不如我们让维罗妮卡消失吧？
why don't we make Veronika disappear?
不
No.
你赢不了
You don't win.
- 我是范德伯格家族的人 - 她在那
- I'm the Vanderberg family!-There she is.
这会儿就开始想你了
Miss you already.
最终揭秘 - 听见了吗？
Final reveal!-Do you hear me?
真正的维罗妮卡·范德伯格
The real Veronika Vanderberg.
范德伯格家绝不会输
The Vanderbergs do not lose!
这世界充满了幻觉
The world is full of illusions.
其中最大的幻觉就是
One of the biggest is that this diamond.
这颗钻石属于范德伯格家族
belongs to the Vanderbergs at all.
作为我父亲唯一没进监狱的亲属
As my father's only un-incarcerated next of kin,
我会确保我们的每一个非法买家
I'll make sure every one of our illicit buyers.
都受到法律的制裁
faces legal repercussions.
然后我会捐出我们所有的资产
And then I'll gift all our assets,
包括“海洋之心”
including the Heart,
捐给它们原本所属的南非社区
to the South African communities they came from.
顺便给在座的各位留点零花钱
with a few extra dollars left for all of you.
看骑士的表演总能让人满载而归
Horsemen crowds always leave with deeper pockets.
- 变相不错 - 名师出高徒
- Nice trick. - I learned from the best.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢大家的加入 谢谢所有人
Thank you for joining us, all of us.
请记住
And please remember,
无论生活给你发了什么牌
no matter what cards life deals you,
你都要学会创造属于自己的奇迹
you have to learn to make your own magic.
女士们先生们…
Ladies and gentlemen…
我们是骑士 晚安
ALL: We are the Horsemen.Good night.
骑士
♪ What Do We Ever Really Know？- Balu Brigada ♪
♪ 阿里得了分 ♪
♪ Ali made a score ♪
♪ 赚了百万还想要更多… ♪
♪ Made a milli Wanted more… ♪
好了 你想要什么
All right, what do you want,
石榴味还是波森莓味？
pomegranate or boysenberry?
哥们 我说我要喝酒
Dude, I said I wanted a drink.
尝尝嘛
Just give it a try.
现在的孩子啊
Kids today.
- 嗯 - 必须的
- Mm!-Of course.
挺好喝
That's pretty good.
- 要尝尝吗？ - 不要
- You wanna try? - No.
好像是你掉的
I think you dropped this.
噢 我的旧卡片
Oh. My old card.
万一你想把它裱起来呢
Just in case you wanna frame it.
谢了 没准真会
Thanks. I might.
真不敢相信你居然是范德伯格家的人
You know, I still cannot believe you're a Vanderberg.
她也不敢信
Neither could she.
我在想
I was thinking I feel like.
我们应该组个自己的团 姐妹们
we should start our own group, you guys.
- 女子魔术团？ - 对对对
- A girls magic group? - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- 没错 - 骑士女孩
- Yes. - The Hor… Horsegirls.
- 不 别叫那个 等等 女骑士
- No. Not that. - Wait, Horsewomen.
- 不要那个 - 骏马女士
- Not that. - Ladies of the Horse.
- 肯定不叫那个 - 小马驹
- It wouldn't be that. - Ponies!
- 真难听 - 是吗？
- That's really bad. - Yeah?
能跟你聊两句吗？
Can I talk to you real quick?
亨利和噢
HENLEY AND Ooh!
我不是想打入“女骑士”内部啊
I'm not trying to infiltrate the Horsewomen.
怎么… 怎么了？
What… what's up?
呃…
Um…
- 就是… - 说啊
- It's just… - Speak.
你怎么了？出什么事了？
What is the matter with you?What's wrong?
很难开口 因为我不…
It's hard because I don't…
我不知道你怎么想
I don't know how you feel.
所以…
And so…
嘿 呃 大家
Hey, uh, everybody.
大家 都过来一下 来
Everybody, come on over here, please.
嗯？来吧 伙计们
Yeah? Come on, guys.
嘿 博斯科 能再拿点那个好吃的东西吗？
Hey, can you grab some more of those delicious things, Bosco?
你们肯定会喜欢的这玩意 绝了
You are gonna love this stuff.It is slap.
- 不 梅里特 别说了 - 真绝了
- No, Merritt, please. - It slaps.
我是想说这东西不错
What I meant to say is it's good.
对 好吧
Yeah. Right.
好吧 那就由我来说吧
Yes, and I will be the one to say it.
我会想你们的
I'm going to miss you guys.
我也正这么想
I was just thinking the same thing.
是啊 我也是
Yeah. Me, too.
该死 我爱你们
Damn it, I love you guys.
- 噢 - 我们也爱你
- Aw. - We love you, too.
我们爱你
We love you.
- 真可爱 - 我也是
- Adorable. - Me, too.
甜死人了 也爱我？
Very sweet. Even me?
真的？你肯定喝高了
Really? You must be very drunk.
哇哦
Whoa.
- 天啊 - 换个话题吧
- Oh, my God. - Just talk about something else.
回到刚才… 我们相亲相爱
Go back to what…We all love each other.
你爱他 他爱她 碰拳 碰拳
You love him, he loves her.Fist bump. Fist bump.
你们俩爱得更深
You guys love each other more.
噢
Oh.
你们有客人？
You guys expecting someone?
没人知道我们在这儿
No one's supposed to know where we are.
- 谁寄的？ - 没写
- Who's it from? - Doesn't say.
打开
Open it.
你开
You open it.
好吧
Okay.
噢 那是… 那是门上那玩意
Oh, that's the… that's the thing from the door.
对 古堡里的 噢 对
Yeah, from the chateau.Oh, yeah!
你 呃… 介意我再试一次吗？
Do you, uh… You mind if I take another crack at it?
- 行 行 你来 - 好？
- Yeah, yeah, go for it. - Yeah?
这回我能搞定
I think I can handle it this time.
你好啊 骑士们
Hello, Horsemen.
想我了吗？
Did you miss me?
迪伦
Dylan.
你不是该在监狱里吗？
But he's supposed to be in prison.
我知道你们在想什么 “他骗了我们”
I know what you're thinking."He lied to us."
但我… 我没骗你们
But I… I didn't lie to you.
我只是让你们相信了非真相的事实
I just led you to believe something that wasn't true.
但这都是为你们好 相信我
But it was for your own good, trust me.
这谜题比你们想像的要深
There's more to this mystery than you realize.
而最终结果就是
And the end result.
魔术骑士团重组了
is that the Horsemen are back together again.
我心里很温暖
It warms my heart.
至于你们三个冒牌货
Now, for you three imposters,
胆敢假装
brazenly pretending like.
是我们绝密组织的成员？
you're part of our top secret organization?
你们以为这样
You think you're gonna get away with it.
还能全身而退 不用付出代价？
with no consequences or repercussions?
好吧…
Well…
你们想对了
you thought right.
- 嘿 - 欢迎
- Hey!-Welcome.
欢迎加入天眼
Welcome to The Eye.
至于其他人
As for the rest of you,
你们以为活干完了
you thought your work was done.
再想想 伙计们
Think again, team.
好戏才刚开场
You're just getting started.
魔术怎么玩？
What's the trick?
字幕制作：leslie727
&
葫 芦 Q群：491019388
♪ Lucky - Reneé Rapp ♪
♪ Hurry up ♪
♪ I swear to God I'm out of patience ♪
♪ I pull up ♪
♪ With or without an invitation ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm so fly And I'm so money ♪
♪ Baby， you can look But don't get touchy ♪
♪ I go fast baby， I go hard ♪
♪ But don't leave a scratch when I crash my car ♪
♪ Steppin' on stars on the boulevard ♪
♪ I find it kinda funny ♪
♪ I get so la-la-la lucky ♪
♪ Okay， got my way ♪
♪ It's almost like I'm Renee ♪
♪ Oh no， where'd I go？♪
♪ Now you see me Now you don't ♪
♪ Okay， got my way ♪
♪ It's almost like I'm Renee ♪
♪ Oh no， where'd I go ♪
♪ Now you see me Now you don't ♪
♪ I go fast baby， I go hard ♪
♪ But don't leave a scratch when I crash my car ♪
♪ Steppin' on stars on the boulevard ♪
♪ I find it kinda funny ♪
♪ I get so la-la-la lucky ♪
♪ La-la-la-lucky ♪
♪ I find it kinda funny ♪
♪ I get so la-la-la lucky ♪
♪ La-la-la-lucky ♪
♪ Hear me out ♪
♪ I've never been too good at listenin' ♪
♪ I'm good at getting what I want ♪
♪ Don't need forgiveness or permission ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm so fly And I'm so money ♪
♪ Baby， you can look But don't get touchy ♪
♪ I go fast baby， I go hard ♪
♪ But don't leave a scratch when I crash my car ♪
♪ Steppin' on stars on the boulevard ♪
♪ I find it kinda funny ♪
♪ I get so la-la-la lucky ♪
♪ La-la-la-lucky ♪
♪ I find it kinda funny ♪
♪ I get so la-la-la lucky ♪